{"question": "A small grey SUV is travelling along the highway slightly in front of the camera to the right. As it comes upon an intersection a black SUV without the right of way enters. The grey SUV slams on the brakes to no avail. The two vehicles collide with each other. Could the accident be prevented if no vehicles were speeding or driving recklessly?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 0}
{"question": "A small grey SUV is travelling along the highway slightly in front of the camera to the right. As it comes upon an intersection a black SUV without the right of way enters. The grey SUV slams on the brakes to no avail. The two vehicles collide with each other. Could the accident be prevented if a convex mirror is installed at the turning point?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes, there would be no obstructed views"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 1}
{"question": "A small grey SUV is travelling along the highway slightly in front of the camera to the right. As it comes upon an intersection a black SUV without the right of way enters. The grey SUV slams on the brakes to no avail. The two vehicles collide with each other. Could the accident be prevented if no vehicles make sudden movements?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 2}
{"question": "A small grey SUV is travelling along the highway slightly in front of the camera to the right. As it comes upon an intersection a black SUV without the right of way enters. The grey SUV slams on the brakes to no avail. The two vehicles collide with each other. Could any involved vehicles stop in time to prevent the accident?", "candidates": ["No, there was no time to react", "Yes, there was enough time to react"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 3}
{"question": "A small grey SUV is travelling along the highway slightly in front of the camera to the right. As it comes upon an intersection a black SUV without the right of way enters. The grey SUV slams on the brakes to no avail. The two vehicles collide with each other. Could the accident be prevented if all vehicles drive in the correct direction?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 4}
{"question": "The car with the camera is driving down an icy road. A dark colored car trys to merge to the left lane. The dark car lost control of direction. The dark car hits on the road side. Could the accident be prevented if no vehicles were speeding or driving recklessly?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 5}
{"question": "The car with the camera is driving down an icy road. A dark colored car trys to merge to the left lane. The dark car lost control of direction. The dark car hits on the road side. Could the accident be prevented if the weather is suitable for driving?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 6}
{"question": "The car with the camera is driving down an icy road. A dark colored car trys to merge to the left lane. The dark car lost control of direction. The dark car hits on the road side. Could the accident be prevented if the roads are marked clearly?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes, the vehicles would stay in their lane"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 7}
{"question": "The car with the camera is driving down an icy road. A dark colored car trys to merge to the left lane. The dark car lost control of direction. The dark car hits on the road side. Could the accident be prevented if no vehicles make sudden movements?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 8}
{"question": "The car with the camera is driving down an icy road. A dark colored car trys to merge to the left lane. The dark car lost control of direction. The dark car hits on the road side. Could the accident be prevented if the involved vehicles check for safety before making a move?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 9}
{"question": "A car driving slowly through a narrow road with many pedestrians and vehicles. A pedestrian appears to be walking into the car's path from the right. The car narrowly passes by a black sedan on the left to avoid hitting the pedestrian who did not pay enough attention to the road. How can this road infrastructure be improved to prevent future accident?", "candidates": ["The road can have physical barrier between two directions", "The road can be larger"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 10}
{"question": "A car driving slowly through a narrow road with many pedestrians and vehicles. A pedestrian appears to be walking into the car's path from the right. The car narrowly passes by a black sedan on the left to avoid hitting the pedestrian who did not pay enough attention to the road. How can this road infrastructure be improved to prevent future accident?", "candidates": ["The road can have more lanes", "The road can have better makings", "Others", "Nothing to improve"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 11}
{"question": "A car driving slowly through a narrow road with many pedestrians and vehicles. A pedestrian appears to be walking into the car's path from the right. The car narrowly passes by a black sedan on the left to avoid hitting the pedestrian who did not pay enough attention to the road. Can this road infrastructure prevent collision against pedestrians?", "candidates": ["No, there is no sidewalk", "Yes, there are large dedicated sidewalks", "No, sidewalks are too small"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 12}
{"question": "A car driving slowly through a narrow road with many pedestrians and vehicles. A pedestrian appears to be walking into the car's path from the right. The car narrowly passes by a black sedan on the left to avoid hitting the pedestrian who did not pay enough attention to the road. What are the main reasons that no accidents occurred in this video?", "candidates": ["The road is big enough", "Others", "The road is clearly marked", "The traffic rules are well observed and followed"], "answer": 3, "class": "I", "id": 13}
{"question": "A car driving slowly through a narrow road with many pedestrians and vehicles. A pedestrian appears to be walking into the car's path from the right. The car narrowly passes by a black sedan on the left to avoid hitting the pedestrian who did not pay enough attention to the road. Can this road infrastucture prevent side collision?", "candidates": ["No, the road is too small", "Yes, the road is big enough", "No, the road is unmarked", "Yes, the road is marked clearly"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 14}
{"question": "A silver sedan and a gray truck are stationary at an intersection. A sed sedan is staying behind the gray truck. A pedestrian crosses in front of the silver sedan and gray truck. The red sedan suddenly moves to the back of the gray truck and hits it from behind. After being hit the gray truck moves slightly forward. The pedestrian crosses the road unhurt. Could any involved vehicles stop in time to prevent the accident?", "candidates": ["Yes, there was enough time to react", "No, there was no time to react"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 15}
{"question": "A silver sedan and a gray truck are stationary at an intersection. A sed sedan is staying behind the gray truck. A pedestrian crosses in front of the silver sedan and gray truck. The red sedan suddenly moves to the back of the gray truck and hits it from behind. After being hit the gray truck moves slightly forward. The pedestrian crosses the road unhurt. Could the accident be prevented if no vehicles make sudden movements?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 16}
{"question": "A silver sedan and a gray truck are stationary at an intersection. A sed sedan is staying behind the gray truck. A pedestrian crosses in front of the silver sedan and gray truck. The red sedan suddenly moves to the back of the gray truck and hits it from behind. After being hit the gray truck moves slightly forward. The pedestrian crosses the road unhurt. Could the accident be prevented if the road infrastructure is better?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes, better markings will help", "Yes, better road surface will help", "Yes, more street signs will help"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 17}
{"question": "A silver sedan and a gray truck are stationary at an intersection. A sed sedan is staying behind the gray truck. A pedestrian crosses in front of the silver sedan and gray truck. The red sedan suddenly moves to the back of the gray truck and hits it from behind. After being hit the gray truck moves slightly forward. The pedestrian crosses the road unhurt. Could any involved vehicles steer away to prevent the accident?", "candidates": ["No, there was no space", "No, there was no time to react", "Yes, there was enough space"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 18}
{"question": "A silver sedan and a gray truck are stationary at an intersection. A sed sedan is staying behind the gray truck. A pedestrian crosses in front of the silver sedan and gray truck. The red sedan suddenly moves to the back of the gray truck and hits it from behind. After being hit the gray truck moves slightly forward. The pedestrian crosses the road unhurt. Could the accident be prevented if no vehicles were speeding or driving recklessly?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 19}
{"question": "A vehicle is paused behind a black truck which is resting in the road. A white truck going the opposite direction in the wrong lane quickly approaches and crashes into the front of black truck. The black truck is pushed into the vehicle in the rear. The white truck, black truck, and vehicle move backwards briefly before coming to a rest. Could the accident be prevented if the road infrastructure is better?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes, better markings will help", "Yes, larger road will help", "Yes, more street signs will help"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 20}
{"question": "A vehicle is paused behind a black truck which is resting in the road. A white truck going the opposite direction in the wrong lane quickly approaches and crashes into the front of black truck. The black truck is pushed into the vehicle in the rear. The white truck, black truck, and vehicle move backwards briefly before coming to a rest. Could the accident be prevented if the involved vehicles check for safety before making a move?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 21}
{"question": "A vehicle is paused behind a black truck which is resting in the road. A white truck going the opposite direction in the wrong lane quickly approaches and crashes into the front of black truck. The black truck is pushed into the vehicle in the rear. The white truck, black truck, and vehicle move backwards briefly before coming to a rest. Could the accident be prevented if the roads are marked clearly?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes, the vehicles would stay in their lane"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 22}
{"question": "A vehicle is paused behind a black truck which is resting in the road. A white truck going the opposite direction in the wrong lane quickly approaches and crashes into the front of black truck. The black truck is pushed into the vehicle in the rear. The white truck, black truck, and vehicle move backwards briefly before coming to a rest. Could the accident be prevented if all vehicles drive in the correct direction?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 23}
{"question": "A vehicle is paused behind a black truck which is resting in the road. A white truck going the opposite direction in the wrong lane quickly approaches and crashes into the front of black truck. The black truck is pushed into the vehicle in the rear. The white truck, black truck, and vehicle move backwards briefly before coming to a rest. Could any involved vehicles stop in time to prevent the accident?", "candidates": ["Yes, there was enough time to react", "No, there was no time to react"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 24}
{"question": "The POV car is turning to the left with a heavy traffic on its left. A white truck driving in the wrong lane quickly approaches the POV car. The white truck crashes into the POV car on its left. The white truck pauses in the road. The POV car is pushed back slightly before pausing in the road. The hood of the POV car is crumpled up slightly. Could any involved vehicles steer away to prevent the accident?", "candidates": ["No, there was no space", "Yes, there was enough space", "No, there was no time to react"], "answer": 2, "class": "I", "id": 25}
{"question": "The POV car is turning to the left with a heavy traffic on its left. A white truck driving in the wrong lane quickly approaches the POV car. The white truck crashes into the POV car on its left. The white truck pauses in the road. The POV car is pushed back slightly before pausing in the road. The hood of the POV car is crumpled up slightly. Could the accident be prevented if all vehicles drive in the correct direction?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 26}
{"question": "The POV car is turning to the left with a heavy traffic on its left. A white truck driving in the wrong lane quickly approaches the POV car. The white truck crashes into the POV car on its left. The white truck pauses in the road. The POV car is pushed back slightly before pausing in the road. The hood of the POV car is crumpled up slightly. Could the accident be prevented if the involved vehicles change lane or turn properly?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 27}
{"question": "The POV car is turning to the left with a heavy traffic on its left. A white truck driving in the wrong lane quickly approaches the POV car. The white truck crashes into the POV car on its left. The white truck pauses in the road. The POV car is pushed back slightly before pausing in the road. The hood of the POV car is crumpled up slightly. Could the accident be prevented if the road infrastructure is better?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes, better markings will help", "Yes, more street signs will help", "Yes, better road surface will help"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 28}
{"question": "The POV car is turning to the left with a heavy traffic on its left. A white truck driving in the wrong lane quickly approaches the POV car. The white truck crashes into the POV car on its left. The white truck pauses in the road. The POV car is pushed back slightly before pausing in the road. The hood of the POV car is crumpled up slightly. Could the accident be prevented if a convex mirror is installed at the turning point?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes, there would be no obstructed views"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 29}
{"question": "A silver car ahead makes a stop at the stop sign and starts to move after stop. Another car from the left is driving quickly into the intersection without stopping in the stop sign. The sliver car ahead collides the side of the car coming from left.  Both of the car stopped after the collision. Could the accident be prevented if the involved vehicles check for safety before making a move?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 30}
{"question": "A silver car ahead makes a stop at the stop sign and starts to move after stop. Another car from the left is driving quickly into the intersection without stopping in the stop sign. The sliver car ahead collides the side of the car coming from left.  Both of the car stopped after the collision. Could the accident be prevented if no vehicles were speeding or driving recklessly?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 31}
{"question": "A silver car ahead makes a stop at the stop sign and starts to move after stop. Another car from the left is driving quickly into the intersection without stopping in the stop sign. The sliver car ahead collides the side of the car coming from left.  Both of the car stopped after the collision. Could the accident be prevented if the involved vehicles change lane or turn properly?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 32}
{"question": "A silver car ahead makes a stop at the stop sign and starts to move after stop. Another car from the left is driving quickly into the intersection without stopping in the stop sign. The sliver car ahead collides the side of the car coming from left.  Both of the car stopped after the collision. Could any involved vehicles stop in time to prevent the accident?", "candidates": ["No, there was no time to react", "Yes, there was enough time to react"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 33}
{"question": "A silver car ahead makes a stop at the stop sign and starts to move after stop. Another car from the left is driving quickly into the intersection without stopping in the stop sign. The sliver car ahead collides the side of the car coming from left.  Both of the car stopped after the collision. Could the accident be prevented if no vehicles make sudden movements?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 34}
{"question": "A car drives on a narrow road that starts to bend to the right, with a pickup approaching from the opposite direction. Despite having a clear line of sight, the pickup drives into the path of the car. The pickup turns too late to avoid the collision, hits the car and the car stops immediately. Could the accident be prevented if the involved vehicles change lane or turn properly?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 35}
{"question": "A car drives on a narrow road that starts to bend to the right, with a pickup approaching from the opposite direction. Despite having a clear line of sight, the pickup drives into the path of the car. The pickup turns too late to avoid the collision, hits the car and the car stops immediately. Could the accident be prevented if no vehicles make sudden movements?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 36}
{"question": "A car drives on a narrow road that starts to bend to the right, with a pickup approaching from the opposite direction. Despite having a clear line of sight, the pickup drives into the path of the car. The pickup turns too late to avoid the collision, hits the car and the car stops immediately. Could any involved vehicles stop in time to prevent the accident?", "candidates": ["No, there was no time to react", "Yes, there was enough time to react"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 37}
{"question": "A car drives on a narrow road that starts to bend to the right, with a pickup approaching from the opposite direction. Despite having a clear line of sight, the pickup drives into the path of the car. The pickup turns too late to avoid the collision, hits the car and the car stops immediately. Could the accident be prevented if the weather is suitable for driving?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 38}
{"question": "A car drives on a narrow road that starts to bend to the right, with a pickup approaching from the opposite direction. Despite having a clear line of sight, the pickup drives into the path of the car. The pickup turns too late to avoid the collision, hits the car and the car stops immediately. Could the accident be prevented if all vehicles drive in the correct direction?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 39}
{"question": "A white Prius is in the middle of an intersection failry slowly completing a right turn. A bicycle enters the intersection and crosses in front of the white Prius. The white Prius continues straight when the bicyclist hit the white Prius badly. The bicyclist is thrown off the bicycle and hits the hood of the white Prius before falling to the ground. The white Prius remains resting in the intersection with the bicyclist on the road in front. Could any involved vehicles stop in time to prevent the accident?", "candidates": ["Yes, there was enough time to react", "No, there was no time to react"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 40}
{"question": "A white Prius is in the middle of an intersection failry slowly completing a right turn. A bicycle enters the intersection and crosses in front of the white Prius. The white Prius continues straight when the bicyclist hit the white Prius badly. The bicyclist is thrown off the bicycle and hits the hood of the white Prius before falling to the ground. The white Prius remains resting in the intersection with the bicyclist on the road in front. Could the accident be prevented if no vehicles make sudden movements?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 41}
{"question": "A white Prius is in the middle of an intersection failry slowly completing a right turn. A bicycle enters the intersection and crosses in front of the white Prius. The white Prius continues straight when the bicyclist hit the white Prius badly. The bicyclist is thrown off the bicycle and hits the hood of the white Prius before falling to the ground. The white Prius remains resting in the intersection with the bicyclist on the road in front. Could the accident be prevented if the weather is suitable for driving?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 42}
{"question": "A white Prius is in the middle of an intersection failry slowly completing a right turn. A bicycle enters the intersection and crosses in front of the white Prius. The white Prius continues straight when the bicyclist hit the white Prius badly. The bicyclist is thrown off the bicycle and hits the hood of the white Prius before falling to the ground. The white Prius remains resting in the intersection with the bicyclist on the road in front. Could the accident be prevented if the roads are marked clearly?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes, the vehicles would stay in their lane"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 43}
{"question": "A white Prius is in the middle of an intersection failry slowly completing a right turn. A bicycle enters the intersection and crosses in front of the white Prius. The white Prius continues straight when the bicyclist hit the white Prius badly. The bicyclist is thrown off the bicycle and hits the hood of the white Prius before falling to the ground. The white Prius remains resting in the intersection with the bicyclist on the road in front. Could the accident be prevented if the involved vehicles check for safety before making a move?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 44}
{"question": "The POV car is quickly going down a highway. The POV car approaches an intersection. There is a red sedan in the opposing lane waiting to turn and cross the intersection. The red sedan quickly makes a left turn when the POV car enter the intersection. The POV car veers to the right. The red sedan hits the side of the POV car. Could the accident be prevented if the weather is suitable for driving?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 45}
{"question": "The POV car is quickly going down a highway. The POV car approaches an intersection. There is a red sedan in the opposing lane waiting to turn and cross the intersection. The red sedan quickly makes a left turn when the POV car enter the intersection. The POV car veers to the right. The red sedan hits the side of the POV car. Could the accident be prevented if the involved vehicles change lane or turn properly?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 46}
{"question": "The POV car is quickly going down a highway. The POV car approaches an intersection. There is a red sedan in the opposing lane waiting to turn and cross the intersection. The red sedan quickly makes a left turn when the POV car enter the intersection. The POV car veers to the right. The red sedan hits the side of the POV car. Could the accident be prevented if all vehicles keep a safe distance away from one another?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 47}
{"question": "The POV car is quickly going down a highway. The POV car approaches an intersection. There is a red sedan in the opposing lane waiting to turn and cross the intersection. The red sedan quickly makes a left turn when the POV car enter the intersection. The POV car veers to the right. The red sedan hits the side of the POV car. Could any involved vehicles steer away to prevent the accident?", "candidates": ["No, there was no time to react", "Yes, there was enough space", "No, there was no enough space"], "answer": 2, "class": "I", "id": 48}
{"question": "The POV car is quickly going down a highway. The POV car approaches an intersection. There is a red sedan in the opposing lane waiting to turn and cross the intersection. The red sedan quickly makes a left turn when the POV car enter the intersection. The POV car veers to the right. The red sedan hits the side of the POV car. Could any involved vehicles stop in time to prevent the accident?", "candidates": ["Yes, there was enough time to react", "No, there was no time to react"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 49}
{"question": "The POV vehicle is driving forwards rather quickly in the left lane. The POV vehicle continues to drive straight quickly. A silver sedan coming from the right is quickly speeding through the interesction without noticing the speeding vehicles. The POV vehicle crashes into the silver sedan. The POV vehicle spins around and slowly comes to a stop. Could the accident be prevented if the weather is suitable for driving?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 50}
{"question": "The POV vehicle is driving forwards rather quickly in the left lane. The POV vehicle continues to drive straight quickly. A silver sedan coming from the right is quickly speeding through the interesction without noticing the speeding vehicles. The POV vehicle crashes into the silver sedan. The POV vehicle spins around and slowly comes to a stop. Could the accident be prevented if no vehicles were speeding or driving recklessly?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 51}
{"question": "The POV vehicle is driving forwards rather quickly in the left lane. The POV vehicle continues to drive straight quickly. A silver sedan coming from the right is quickly speeding through the interesction without noticing the speeding vehicles. The POV vehicle crashes into the silver sedan. The POV vehicle spins around and slowly comes to a stop. Could the accident be prevented if a convex mirror is installed at the turning point?", "candidates": ["Yes, there would be no obstructed views", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 52}
{"question": "The POV vehicle is driving forwards rather quickly in the left lane. The POV vehicle continues to drive straight quickly. A silver sedan coming from the right is quickly speeding through the interesction without noticing the speeding vehicles. The POV vehicle crashes into the silver sedan. The POV vehicle spins around and slowly comes to a stop. Could the accident be prevented if the involved vehicles check for safety before making a move?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 53}
{"question": "The POV vehicle is driving forwards rather quickly in the left lane. The POV vehicle continues to drive straight quickly. A silver sedan coming from the right is quickly speeding through the interesction without noticing the speeding vehicles. The POV vehicle crashes into the silver sedan. The POV vehicle spins around and slowly comes to a stop. Could any involved vehicles stop in time to prevent the accident?", "candidates": ["No, there was no time to react", "Yes, there was enough time to react"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 54}
{"question": "A silver SUV approaches an intersection at a fairly rapid pace. The silver SUV enters the intersection keeping up a high pace with the red light on as a silver truck enters the intersection going parallel to the silver SUV at a fairly rapid pace. Both the silver SUV and the silver truck slow down but they still collide each other. The silver truck is turned a bit to the right coming to a stop while the silver SUV remains facing the same direction coming to a rest in the intersection. Could any involved vehicles steer away to prevent the accident?", "candidates": ["No, there was no space", "No, there was no time to react", "Yes, there was enough space"], "answer": 2, "class": "I", "id": 55}
{"question": "A silver SUV approaches an intersection at a fairly rapid pace. The silver SUV enters the intersection keeping up a high pace with the red light on as a silver truck enters the intersection going parallel to the silver SUV at a fairly rapid pace. Both the silver SUV and the silver truck slow down but they still collide each other. The silver truck is turned a bit to the right coming to a stop while the silver SUV remains facing the same direction coming to a rest in the intersection. Could the accident be prevented if no vehicles make sudden movements?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 56}
{"question": "A silver SUV approaches an intersection at a fairly rapid pace. The silver SUV enters the intersection keeping up a high pace with the red light on as a silver truck enters the intersection going parallel to the silver SUV at a fairly rapid pace. Both the silver SUV and the silver truck slow down but they still collide each other. The silver truck is turned a bit to the right coming to a stop while the silver SUV remains facing the same direction coming to a rest in the intersection. Could the accident be prevented if the roads are marked clearly?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes, the vehicles would stay in their lane"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 57}
{"question": "A silver SUV approaches an intersection at a fairly rapid pace. The silver SUV enters the intersection keeping up a high pace with the red light on as a silver truck enters the intersection going parallel to the silver SUV at a fairly rapid pace. Both the silver SUV and the silver truck slow down but they still collide each other. The silver truck is turned a bit to the right coming to a stop while the silver SUV remains facing the same direction coming to a rest in the intersection. Could the accident be prevented if no vehicles were speeding or driving recklessly?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 58}
{"question": "A silver SUV approaches an intersection at a fairly rapid pace. The silver SUV enters the intersection keeping up a high pace with the red light on as a silver truck enters the intersection going parallel to the silver SUV at a fairly rapid pace. Both the silver SUV and the silver truck slow down but they still collide each other. The silver truck is turned a bit to the right coming to a stop while the silver SUV remains facing the same direction coming to a rest in the intersection. Could the accident be prevented if the weather is suitable for driving?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 59}
{"question": "A white van slowly enters an intersection and trys to make a right turn in a snow-coverd road. A darkly colored compact car quickly goes through the intersection in a parallel direction. The darkly colored compact car crashes into the side of the white van. Causing the white van to spin around. The darkly colored compact car passes through the intersection before coming to a rest. The white van remains resting in the intersection facing the opposite direction. The darkly colored compact car drives off in that direction. Could the accident be prevented if the weather is suitable for driving?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 60}
{"question": "A white van slowly enters an intersection and trys to make a right turn in a snow-coverd road. A darkly colored compact car quickly goes through the intersection in a parallel direction. The darkly colored compact car crashes into the side of the white van. Causing the white van to spin around. The darkly colored compact car passes through the intersection before coming to a rest. The white van remains resting in the intersection facing the opposite direction. The darkly colored compact car drives off in that direction. Could the accident be prevented if no vehicles make sudden movements?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 61}
{"question": "A white van slowly enters an intersection and trys to make a right turn in a snow-coverd road. A darkly colored compact car quickly goes through the intersection in a parallel direction. The darkly colored compact car crashes into the side of the white van. Causing the white van to spin around. The darkly colored compact car passes through the intersection before coming to a rest. The white van remains resting in the intersection facing the opposite direction. The darkly colored compact car drives off in that direction. Could the accident be prevented if all vehicles keep a safe distance away from one another?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 62}
{"question": "A white van slowly enters an intersection and trys to make a right turn in a snow-coverd road. A darkly colored compact car quickly goes through the intersection in a parallel direction. The darkly colored compact car crashes into the side of the white van. Causing the white van to spin around. The darkly colored compact car passes through the intersection before coming to a rest. The white van remains resting in the intersection facing the opposite direction. The darkly colored compact car drives off in that direction. Could the accident be prevented if the involved vehicles change lane or turn properly?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 63}
{"question": "A white van slowly enters an intersection and trys to make a right turn in a snow-coverd road. A darkly colored compact car quickly goes through the intersection in a parallel direction. The darkly colored compact car crashes into the side of the white van. Causing the white van to spin around. The darkly colored compact car passes through the intersection before coming to a rest. The white van remains resting in the intersection facing the opposite direction. The darkly colored compact car drives off in that direction. Could any involved vehicles steer away to prevent the accident?", "candidates": ["No, there was no time to react", "Yes, there was enough space", "No, there was no space"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 64}
{"question": "A darkly colored sedan in the left lane is holding still at a red light in a snowy weather. The left turn signal of the darkly colored car is blinking. A second darkly colored sedan in the middle lane is also preparing to make a left turn. A white colored sedan in the right lane is waiting for the light to turn green. The turning light turns green. Both of the darkly colored cars proceed to turn left. The darkly colored sedan in the center lane completes the turn successfully. A silver colored van speeds through the intersection in the direction the darkly colored sedans are turning. The silver van hits the darkly colored sedan. The darkly colored sedan is turned around and proceeds to drive off screen. The bumper of the darkly colored sedan drops off. The silver van is turned to the left. It proceeds to drive towards the sidewalk before coming to a standstill. Could any involved vehicles stop in time to prevent the accident?", "candidates": ["No, there was no time to react", "Yes, there was enough time to react"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 65}
{"question": "A darkly colored sedan in the left lane is holding still at a red light in a snowy weather. The left turn signal of the darkly colored car is blinking. A second darkly colored sedan in the middle lane is also preparing to make a left turn. A white colored sedan in the right lane is waiting for the light to turn green. The turning light turns green. Both of the darkly colored cars proceed to turn left. The darkly colored sedan in the center lane completes the turn successfully. A silver colored van speeds through the intersection in the direction the darkly colored sedans are turning. The silver van hits the darkly colored sedan. The darkly colored sedan is turned around and proceeds to drive off screen. The bumper of the darkly colored sedan drops off. The silver van is turned to the left. It proceeds to drive towards the sidewalk before coming to a standstill. Could the accident be prevented if no vehicles make sudden movements?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 66}
{"question": "A darkly colored sedan in the left lane is holding still at a red light in a snowy weather. The left turn signal of the darkly colored car is blinking. A second darkly colored sedan in the middle lane is also preparing to make a left turn. A white colored sedan in the right lane is waiting for the light to turn green. The turning light turns green. Both of the darkly colored cars proceed to turn left. The darkly colored sedan in the center lane completes the turn successfully. A silver colored van speeds through the intersection in the direction the darkly colored sedans are turning. The silver van hits the darkly colored sedan. The darkly colored sedan is turned around and proceeds to drive off screen. The bumper of the darkly colored sedan drops off. The silver van is turned to the left. It proceeds to drive towards the sidewalk before coming to a standstill. Could the accident be prevented if a convex mirror is installed at the turning point?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes, there would be no obstructed views"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 67}
{"question": "A darkly colored sedan in the left lane is holding still at a red light in a snowy weather. The left turn signal of the darkly colored car is blinking. A second darkly colored sedan in the middle lane is also preparing to make a left turn. A white colored sedan in the right lane is waiting for the light to turn green. The turning light turns green. Both of the darkly colored cars proceed to turn left. The darkly colored sedan in the center lane completes the turn successfully. A silver colored van speeds through the intersection in the direction the darkly colored sedans are turning. The silver van hits the darkly colored sedan. The darkly colored sedan is turned around and proceeds to drive off screen. The bumper of the darkly colored sedan drops off. The silver van is turned to the left. It proceeds to drive towards the sidewalk before coming to a standstill. Could any involved vehicles steer away to prevent the accident?", "candidates": ["No, there was no space", "No, there was no time to react", "Yes, there was enough space"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 68}
{"question": "A darkly colored sedan in the left lane is holding still at a red light in a snowy weather. The left turn signal of the darkly colored car is blinking. A second darkly colored sedan in the middle lane is also preparing to make a left turn. A white colored sedan in the right lane is waiting for the light to turn green. The turning light turns green. Both of the darkly colored cars proceed to turn left. The darkly colored sedan in the center lane completes the turn successfully. A silver colored van speeds through the intersection in the direction the darkly colored sedans are turning. The silver van hits the darkly colored sedan. The darkly colored sedan is turned around and proceeds to drive off screen. The bumper of the darkly colored sedan drops off. The silver van is turned to the left. It proceeds to drive towards the sidewalk before coming to a standstill. Could the accident be prevented if the involved vehicles check for safety before making a move?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 69}
{"question": "A darkly colored sedan in the left lane is holding still at a red light in a snowy weather. The left turn signal of the darkly colored car is blinking. A second darkly colored sedan in the middle lane is also preparing to make a left turn. A white colored sedan in the right lane is waiting for the light to turn green. The turning light turns green. Both of the darkly colored cars proceed to turn left. The darkly colored sedan in the center lane completes the turn successfully. A silver colored van speeds through the intersection in the direction the darkly colored sedans are turning. The silver van hits the darkly colored sedan. The darkly colored sedan is turned around and proceeds to drive off screen. The bumper of the darkly colored sedan drops off. The silver van is turned to the left. It proceeds to drive towards the sidewalk before coming to a standstill. Could the accident be prevented if there is no traffic light violation?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 70}
{"question": "A darkly colored sedan in the left lane is holding still at a red light in a snowy weather. The left turn signal of the darkly colored car is blinking. A second darkly colored sedan in the middle lane is also preparing to make a left turn. A white colored sedan in the right lane is waiting for the light to turn green. The turning light turns green. Both of the darkly colored cars proceed to turn left. The darkly colored sedan in the center lane completes the turn successfully. A silver colored van speeds through the intersection in the direction the darkly colored sedans are turning. The silver van hits the darkly colored sedan. The darkly colored sedan is turned around and proceeds to drive off screen. The bumper of the darkly colored sedan drops off. The silver van is turned to the left. It proceeds to drive towards the sidewalk before coming to a standstill. Could the accident be prevented if the weather is suitable for driving?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 71}
{"question": "A gray oncoming SUV starts to turn his left infront of the POV car. The POV car stops waiting for the gray SUV. A red car comes quickly in the right lane. The gray SUV turns into the red car's lane, and the red car doesn't stop. The red car hits the gray SUV on its side. Could the accident be prevented if the involved vehicles check for safety before making a move?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 72}
{"question": "A gray oncoming SUV starts to turn his left infront of the POV car. The POV car stops waiting for the gray SUV. A red car comes quickly in the right lane. The gray SUV turns into the red car's lane, and the red car doesn't stop. The red car hits the gray SUV on its side. Could the accident be prevented if the roads are marked clearly?", "candidates": ["Yes, the vehicles would stay in their lane", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 73}
{"question": "A gray oncoming SUV starts to turn his left infront of the POV car. The POV car stops waiting for the gray SUV. A red car comes quickly in the right lane. The gray SUV turns into the red car's lane, and the red car doesn't stop. The red car hits the gray SUV on its side. Could the accident be prevented if a convex mirror is installed at the turning point?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes, there would be no obstructed views"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 74}
{"question": "A gray oncoming SUV starts to turn his left infront of the POV car. The POV car stops waiting for the gray SUV. A red car comes quickly in the right lane. The gray SUV turns into the red car's lane, and the red car doesn't stop. The red car hits the gray SUV on its side. Could the accident be prevented if the weather is suitable for driving?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 75}
{"question": "A gray oncoming SUV starts to turn his left infront of the POV car. The POV car stops waiting for the gray SUV. A red car comes quickly in the right lane. The gray SUV turns into the red car's lane, and the red car doesn't stop. The red car hits the gray SUV on its side. Could any involved vehicles stop in time to prevent the accident?", "candidates": ["No, there was no time to react", "Yes, there was enough time to react"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 76}
{"question": "The POV car is going down a nearly-empty three lane road and is aproaching an intersection without traffic light and stop-sign. A black SUV is crossing three lanes on the other left side of the intersection. The black SUV proceeds to cross on the side of the road that the POV car is driving down. The POV car crashes into the side of the black SUV. The black SUV spins 180 degrees and reverses briefly before coming to a stop. Could the accident be prevented if the roads are marked clearly?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes, the vehicles would stop in time"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 77}
{"question": "The POV car is going down a nearly-empty three lane road and is aproaching an intersection without traffic light and stop-sign. A black SUV is crossing three lanes on the other left side of the intersection. The black SUV proceeds to cross on the side of the road that the POV car is driving down. The POV car crashes into the side of the black SUV. The black SUV spins 180 degrees and reverses briefly before coming to a stop. Could the accident be prevented if all vehicles keep a safe distance away from one another?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 78}
{"question": "The POV car is going down a nearly-empty three lane road and is aproaching an intersection without traffic light and stop-sign. A black SUV is crossing three lanes on the other left side of the intersection. The black SUV proceeds to cross on the side of the road that the POV car is driving down. The POV car crashes into the side of the black SUV. The black SUV spins 180 degrees and reverses briefly before coming to a stop. Could the accident be prevented if the involved vehicles check for safety before making a move?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 79}
{"question": "The POV car is going down a nearly-empty three lane road and is aproaching an intersection without traffic light and stop-sign. A black SUV is crossing three lanes on the other left side of the intersection. The black SUV proceeds to cross on the side of the road that the POV car is driving down. The POV car crashes into the side of the black SUV. The black SUV spins 180 degrees and reverses briefly before coming to a stop. Could the accident be prevented if the road infrastructure is better?", "candidates": ["Yes, more street signs will help", "Yes, better road surface will help", "Yes, better markings will help", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 80}
{"question": "The POV car is going down a nearly-empty three lane road and is aproaching an intersection without traffic light and stop-sign. A black SUV is crossing three lanes on the other left side of the intersection. The black SUV proceeds to cross on the side of the road that the POV car is driving down. The POV car crashes into the side of the black SUV. The black SUV spins 180 degrees and reverses briefly before coming to a stop. Could the accident be prevented if the involved vehicles change lane or turn properly?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 81}
{"question": "The POV car is approaching an intersection in a moderate traffic, slowing down. The POV car drives into the left-turn lane. A black sedan, that has been turning from the left into the opposite-direction lane,  fails to complete to turn within its lane and gets slightly into the POV car's path. The POV car tries to avoid the contact by quickly turning to the right, but the POV still gets hit ftom the side and stops. Could any involved vehicles stop in time to prevent the accident?", "candidates": ["No, there was no time to react", "Yes, there was enough time to react"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 82}
{"question": "The POV car is approaching an intersection in a moderate traffic, slowing down. The POV car drives into the left-turn lane. A black sedan, that has been turning from the left into the opposite-direction lane,  fails to complete to turn within its lane and gets slightly into the POV car's path. The POV car tries to avoid the contact by quickly turning to the right, but the POV still gets hit ftom the side and stops. Could the accident be prevented if the road infrastructure is better?", "candidates": ["Yes, better markings will help", "Yes, better road surface will help", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes, more street signs will help"], "answer": 2, "class": "I", "id": 83}
{"question": "The POV car is approaching an intersection in a moderate traffic, slowing down. The POV car drives into the left-turn lane. A black sedan, that has been turning from the left into the opposite-direction lane,  fails to complete to turn within its lane and gets slightly into the POV car's path. The POV car tries to avoid the contact by quickly turning to the right, but the POV still gets hit ftom the side and stops. Could the accident be prevented if the involved vehicles change lane or turn properly?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 84}
{"question": "The POV car is approaching an intersection in a moderate traffic, slowing down. The POV car drives into the left-turn lane. A black sedan, that has been turning from the left into the opposite-direction lane,  fails to complete to turn within its lane and gets slightly into the POV car's path. The POV car tries to avoid the contact by quickly turning to the right, but the POV still gets hit ftom the side and stops. Could any involved vehicles steer away to prevent the accident?", "candidates": ["Yes, there was enough space", "No, there was no time to react", "No, there was no space"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 85}
{"question": "The POV car is approaching an intersection in a moderate traffic, slowing down. The POV car drives into the left-turn lane. A black sedan, that has been turning from the left into the opposite-direction lane,  fails to complete to turn within its lane and gets slightly into the POV car's path. The POV car tries to avoid the contact by quickly turning to the right, but the POV still gets hit ftom the side and stops. Could the accident be prevented if the involved vehicles check for safety before making a move?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 86}
{"question": "The POV car merged onto the road from a parking slot. A black car is driving from the back of the road. The black car hits the POV car on its side. The black car is pointed to the other side of the road. Did an accident happen?", "candidates": ["Yes, the vehicle(s) are in unusual positions", "No, no vehicles receive any damage", "Yes, there are visible damages"], "answer": 2, "class": "R", "id": 87}
{"question": "The POV car merged onto the road from a parking slot. A black car is driving from the back of the road. The black car hits the POV car on its side. The black car is pointed to the other side of the road. Which could be the reason for this accident?", "candidates": ["Improper lane change", "Road safety negligence", "Traffic congestion", "Speeding vehicles"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 88}
{"question": "The POV car merged onto the road from a parking slot. A black car is driving from the back of the road. The black car hits the POV car on its side. The black car is pointed to the other side of the road. Did the accident happen when the involved vehicles were changing lane or turning?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 89}
{"question": "The POV car merged onto the road from a parking slot. A black car is driving from the back of the road. The black car hits the POV car on its side. The black car is pointed to the other side of the road. Did any vehicle(s) try to steer away or stop before crashing?", "candidates": ["No, the invovled vehicles were badly damaged", "Yes, the involved vehicles received nearly no damge"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 90}
{"question": "The POV car merged onto the road from a parking slot. A black car is driving from the back of the road. The black car hits the POV car on its side. The black car is pointed to the other side of the road. Which could be the reason for this accident?", "candidates": ["Obstructed view or limited visibility", "Retrograde vehicles"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 91}
{"question": "A black van stops in the middle of a highway horizontally. A white pickup truck is flipping over sideways in front of the balck van. The POV car is in the right lane to avoid the cars on the shoulder. Which could be the reason for this accident?", "candidates": ["Improper lane change", "Obstructed view or limited visibility", "Speeding vehicles", "Others"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 92}
{"question": "A black van stops in the middle of a highway horizontally. A white pickup truck is flipping over sideways in front of the balck van. The POV car is in the right lane to avoid the cars on the shoulder. Did the accident happen when the involved vehicles were speeding?", "candidates": ["Yes, the involved vehicles continued to speed away", "No", "Yes, the invovled vehicles were badly damaged"], "answer": 2, "class": "R", "id": 93}
{"question": "A black van stops in the middle of a highway horizontally. A white pickup truck is flipping over sideways in front of the balck van. The POV car is in the right lane to avoid the cars on the shoulder. Did an accident happen?", "candidates": ["Yes, there are visible damages", "No, no vehicles receive any damage"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 94}
{"question": "A black van stops in the middle of a highway horizontally. A white pickup truck is flipping over sideways in front of the balck van. The POV car is in the right lane to avoid the cars on the shoulder. How did the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["Side-collision", "The vehicle collided with road infrastructure.", "Head-on collision", "Others"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 95}
{"question": "A black van stops in the middle of a highway horizontally. A white pickup truck is flipping over sideways in front of the balck van. The POV car is in the right lane to avoid the cars on the shoulder. Did any vehicle(s) try to steer away or stop before crashing?", "candidates": ["Yes, the involved vehicles received nearly no damge", "No, the invovled vehicles were badly damaged"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 96}
{"question": "A black sedan coming from the left side attempting to make a left turn crashes into a white truck that was trying to merge right in an intersection with a green light. The black sedan and white truck go forwards into their respective lanes in the intersection. They proceed forwards very slowly.  How did the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["Others", "Ran-off-road collision", "No accident happened", "Side-collision"], "answer": 3, "class": "R", "id": 97}
{"question": "A black sedan coming from the left side attempting to make a left turn crashes into a white truck that was trying to merge right in an intersection with a green light. The black sedan and white truck go forwards into their respective lanes in the intersection. They proceed forwards very slowly.  Which could be the reason for this accident?", "candidates": ["Others", "Retrograde vehicles", "Road safety negligence", "Traffic light violation"], "answer": 2, "class": "R", "id": 98}
{"question": "A black sedan coming from the left side attempting to make a left turn crashes into a white truck that was trying to merge right in an intersection with a green light. The black sedan and white truck go forwards into their respective lanes in the intersection. They proceed forwards very slowly.  Did any vehicle(s) try to steer away or stop before crashing?", "candidates": ["Yes, the involved vehicles received nearly no damge", "No, the invovled vehicles were badly damaged"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 99}
{"question": "The POV car is coming to a stop on the sidewalk which is on the left side of the road. The POV is rocked as if it hit somehting or something hits on it. Which could be the reason for this accident?", "candidates": ["Road safety negligence", "Improper lane change", "Others", "Obstructed view or limited visibility"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 100}
{"question": "The POV car is coming to a stop on the sidewalk which is on the left side of the road. The POV is rocked as if it hit somehting or something hits on it. How fast did the vehicles involved in the accident move before they crash?", "candidates": ["Slower than other vehicles", "Roughly not moving", "Faster than other vehicles"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 101}
{"question": "The POV car is coming to a stop on the sidewalk which is on the left side of the road. The POV is rocked as if it hit somehting or something hits on it. Did the accident happen when the involved vehicles were speeding?", "candidates": ["Yes, the invovled vehicles were badly damaged", "Yes, the involved vehicles continued to speed away", "No"], "answer": 2, "class": "R", "id": 102}
{"question": "The POV car is facig the left of the direction of highway. A black compact car is spinning wildly to the right in the middle of the road in front of the POV car. The black compact car spinning right making a full circle. The black compact car regains control and comes to a pause facing left. The black compact car remains still in the road. Did any vehicle(s) try to steer away or stop before crashing?", "candidates": ["No, the invovled vehicles were badly damaged", "Yes, the involved vehicles received nearly no damge"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 103}
{"question": "The POV car is facig the left of the direction of highway. A black compact car is spinning wildly to the right in the middle of the road in front of the POV car. The black compact car spinning right making a full circle. The black compact car regains control and comes to a pause facing left. The black compact car remains still in the road. Which could be the reason for this accident?", "candidates": ["Improper lane change", "Obstructed view or limited visibility", "No accident happened", "Retrograde vehicles"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 104}
{"question": "The POV car is facig the left of the direction of highway. A black compact car is spinning wildly to the right in the middle of the road in front of the POV car. The black compact car spinning right making a full circle. The black compact car regains control and comes to a pause facing left. The black compact car remains still in the road. Did the accident happen when the involved vehicles were speeding?", "candidates": ["Yes, the involved vehicles continued to speed away", "No", "Yes, the invovled vehicles were badly damaged"], "answer": 2, "class": "R", "id": 105}
{"question": "The POV car is facig the left of the direction of highway. A black compact car is spinning wildly to the right in the middle of the road in front of the POV car. The black compact car spinning right making a full circle. The black compact car regains control and comes to a pause facing left. The black compact car remains still in the road. Which could be the reason for this accident?", "candidates": ["Traffic rules violation", "Improper lane change", "Road safety negligence", "Speeding vehicles"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 106}
{"question": "A lightly colored vehicle facing the opposite direction of the highway stays still. A badly damaged white sedan in the leftmost lane is facing right on the highway.  How did the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["The vehicle collided with road infrastructure.", "Rear-end collision", "Head-on collision", "No accident happened"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 107}
{"question": "A lightly colored vehicle facing the opposite direction of the highway stays still. A badly damaged white sedan in the leftmost lane is facing right on the highway.  Which could be the reason for this accident?", "candidates": ["Others", "Speeding vehicles", "Improper lane change", "Retrograde vehicles"], "answer": 2, "class": "R", "id": 108}
{"question": "A light colored, badly damaged car facing the opposite direction of the road is reversing toward the right side of the road sideway. The light colored car reversed from the left of the road to the right of the road and stopped. Did the accident happen when the involved vehicles were changing lane or turning?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 109}
{"question": "A light colored, badly damaged car facing the opposite direction of the road is reversing toward the right side of the road sideway. The light colored car reversed from the left of the road to the right of the road and stopped. How did the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["Collision with road infrastructure", "Others", "No accident happened"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 110}
{"question": "A light colored, badly damaged car facing the opposite direction of the road is reversing toward the right side of the road sideway. The light colored car reversed from the left of the road to the right of the road and stopped. Did the accident happen when the involved vehicles were speeding?", "candidates": ["Yes, the involved vehicles continued to speed away", "No", "Yes, the invovled vehicles were badly damaged"], "answer": 2, "class": "R", "id": 111}
{"question": "A light colored, badly damaged car facing the opposite direction of the road is reversing toward the right side of the road sideway. The light colored car reversed from the left of the road to the right of the road and stopped. How did the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["Rear-end collision", "The vehicle collided with road infrastructure.", "Head-on collision", "Side-collision"], "answer": 3, "class": "R", "id": 112}
{"question": "A white sedan, white van, and grey sedan have crashed and pasted each other side by side. The three cars are facing the same direction. The three cars are coming together close to the POV car  from the middle of the intersection.  Did the accident happen when the involved vehicles were speeding?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes, the invovled vehicles were badly damaged", "Yes, the involved vehicles continued to speed away"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 113}
{"question": "A white sedan, white van, and grey sedan have crashed and pasted each other side by side. The three cars are facing the same direction. The three cars are coming together close to the POV car  from the middle of the intersection.  Did the accident happen when the involved vehicles were changing lane or turning?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 114}
{"question": "A white sedan, white van, and grey sedan have crashed and pasted each other side by side. The three cars are facing the same direction. The three cars are coming together close to the POV car  from the middle of the intersection.  How did the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["Ran-off-road collision", "Side-collision", "The vehicle collided with road infrastructure.", "Others"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 115}
{"question": "A white sedan, white van, and grey sedan have crashed and pasted each other side by side. The three cars are facing the same direction. The three cars are coming together close to the POV car  from the middle of the intersection.  How many vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["One", "More than five", "Two", "Three to five"], "answer": 3, "class": "R", "id": 116}
{"question": "The POV car is waiting for the signal to turn green. Vehicles on the right road are moving forward. A white sedan in the opposite direction accidentally crossed the road. A quickly moving black sedan from the left lane hit the side of white sedan. The black sedan has stopped moving. The white sedan is moving forward. Would the accident still happen if the involved vehicles change lane or turn properly?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes, theat's not the main cause of the acident"], "answer": 1, "class": "C", "id": 117}
{"question": "The POV car is waiting for the signal to turn green. Vehicles on the right road are moving forward. A white sedan in the opposite direction accidentally crossed the road. A quickly moving black sedan from the left lane hit the side of white sedan. The black sedan has stopped moving. The white sedan is moving forward. Was the main cause of the accident due to unfavorable weather condition?", "candidates": ["No, the involved vehicles also violated other traffic rules", "No, the weather is suitable for driving", "Yes"], "answer": 1, "class": "C", "id": 118}
{"question": "The POV car is waiting for the signal to turn green. Vehicles on the right road are moving forward. A white sedan in the opposite direction accidentally crossed the road. A quickly moving black sedan from the left lane hit the side of white sedan. The black sedan has stopped moving. The white sedan is moving forward. Would the accident still happen if all vehicles drive in their correct lane?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes, the involved vehicles would still violate traffic rules"], "answer": 1, "class": "C", "id": 119}
{"question": "The POV car is waiting for the signal to turn green. Vehicles on the right road are moving forward. A white sedan in the opposite direction accidentally crossed the road. A quickly moving black sedan from the left lane hit the side of white sedan. The black sedan has stopped moving. The white sedan is moving forward. Would the accident still happen if the same scenario happened in a larger road?", "candidates": ["Yes, the involved vehicles would still violate traffic rules", "No, there would be more space to safely avoid the accident"], "answer": 0, "class": "C", "id": 120}
{"question": "The POV car is waiting for the signal to turn green. Vehicles on the right road are moving forward. A white sedan in the opposite direction accidentally crossed the road. A quickly moving black sedan from the left lane hit the side of white sedan. The black sedan has stopped moving. The white sedan is moving forward. What's the reason of this accident?", "candidates": ["Vehicle malfunction", "traffic light violation", "Improper lane change", "Speeding vehicles"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 121}
{"question": "The POV car is traveling forwards at a fairly high rate of speed in the center lane. The POV car enteres the intersection on a green light. A black compact sedan turning left from the opposite direction is passing through the intersection as well. The black compact car hits the POV car. The POV car is spun around. The black sedan comes to a rest on the grassy median on the other side of the intersection facing the opposite direction. What types of vehicles that if get removed from the videos, there won't be an accident?", "candidates": ["Suv or cuv", "Motorcycle or scooter", "POV car", "Sports car or convertible"], "answer": 2, "class": "C", "id": 122}
{"question": "The POV car is traveling forwards at a fairly high rate of speed in the center lane. The POV car enteres the intersection on a green light. A black compact sedan turning left from the opposite direction is passing through the intersection as well. The black compact car hits the POV car. The POV car is spun around. The black sedan comes to a rest on the grassy median on the other side of the intersection facing the opposite direction. Would the accident still happen if the involved vehicles change lane or turn properly?", "candidates": ["Yes, the involved vehicles would still violate traffic rules", "No"], "answer": 1, "class": "C", "id": 123}
{"question": "The POV car is traveling forwards at a fairly high rate of speed in the center lane. The POV car enteres the intersection on a green light. A black compact sedan turning left from the opposite direction is passing through the intersection as well. The black compact car hits the POV car. The POV car is spun around. The black sedan comes to a rest on the grassy median on the other side of the intersection facing the opposite direction. Would the accident still happen if all vehicles drive in their correct lane?", "candidates": ["Yes, the involved vehicles would still violate traffic rules", "No"], "answer": 0, "class": "C", "id": 124}
{"question": "The POV car is traveling forwards at a fairly high rate of speed in the center lane. The POV car enteres the intersection on a green light. A black compact sedan turning left from the opposite direction is passing through the intersection as well. The black compact car hits the POV car. The POV car is spun around. The black sedan comes to a rest on the grassy median on the other side of the intersection facing the opposite direction. Would the accident still happen if the roads have better marking?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes, the involved vehicles would still violate traffic rules"], "answer": 1, "class": "C", "id": 125}
{"question": "The POV car is traveling forwards at a fairly high rate of speed in the center lane. The POV car enteres the intersection on a green light. A black compact sedan turning left from the opposite direction is passing through the intersection as well. The black compact car hits the POV car. The POV car is spun around. The black sedan comes to a rest on the grassy median on the other side of the intersection facing the opposite direction. Would the accident still happen if the involved vehicles move at a lower speed?", "candidates": ["No, the invovled vehicles would have more time to react", "Yes, the involved vehicles would still violate traffic rules"], "answer": 0, "class": "C", "id": 126}
{"question": "The POV car is traveling forwards at a fairly high rate of speed in the center lane. The POV car enteres the intersection on a green light. A black compact sedan turning left from the opposite direction is passing through the intersection as well. The black compact car hits the POV car. The POV car is spun around. The black sedan comes to a rest on the grassy median on the other side of the intersection facing the opposite direction. Which car is primarily responsible for this accident", "candidates": ["The black compact car", "POV car"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 127}
{"question": "A barely visible white pickup is approaching the intersection from the opposite direction of POV car. The intersection have stop sign only on the pickup's direction. The pickup starts passing slowly but accelerates through the intersection. A van suddenly comes from the left of the intersection. The pickup's side is hit by the van, causing it to turn to the right. Both the van and the pickup are standing still side by side. What types of vehicles that if get removed from the videos, there won't be an accident?", "candidates": ["POV car", "Sedan or general car", "Motorcycle or scooter", "Mini van or van"], "answer": 3, "class": "C", "id": 128}
{"question": "A barely visible white pickup is approaching the intersection from the opposite direction of POV car. The intersection have stop sign only on the pickup's direction. The pickup starts passing slowly but accelerates through the intersection. A van suddenly comes from the left of the intersection. The pickup's side is hit by the van, causing it to turn to the right. Both the van and the pickup are standing still side by side. Would the accident still happen if the roads have better marking?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes, the involved vehicles would still violate traffic rules"], "answer": 1, "class": "C", "id": 129}
{"question": "A barely visible white pickup is approaching the intersection from the opposite direction of POV car. The intersection have stop sign only on the pickup's direction. The pickup starts passing slowly but accelerates through the intersection. A van suddenly comes from the left of the intersection. The pickup's side is hit by the van, causing it to turn to the right. Both the van and the pickup are standing still side by side. Would the accident still happen if there are less vehicles on the road?", "candidates": ["Yes, the involved vehicles would still violate traffic rules", "No, the car would be more visiable to each other"], "answer": 1, "class": "C", "id": 130}
{"question": "A barely visible white pickup is approaching the intersection from the opposite direction of POV car. The intersection have stop sign only on the pickup's direction. The pickup starts passing slowly but accelerates through the intersection. A van suddenly comes from the left of the intersection. The pickup's side is hit by the van, causing it to turn to the right. Both the van and the pickup are standing still side by side. Was the main cause of the accident due to speeding vehicles?", "candidates": ["No, the involved vehicles also violated other traffic rules", "Yes"], "answer": 1, "class": "C", "id": 131}
{"question": "A barely visible white pickup is approaching the intersection from the opposite direction of POV car. The intersection have stop sign only on the pickup's direction. The pickup starts passing slowly but accelerates through the intersection. A van suddenly comes from the left of the intersection. The pickup's side is hit by the van, causing it to turn to the right. Both the van and the pickup are standing still side by side. Would the accident still happen if the same scenario happened in a larger road?", "candidates": ["No, there would be more space to safely avoid the accident", "Yes, the involved vehicles would still violate traffic rules"], "answer": 0, "class": "C", "id": 132}
{"question": "A silver SUV is moving very slowly on a road. A black sedan from the back moving very quickly crashes into the silver SUV. The silver SUV is pushed off the road to the left. Both the silver SUV and the black sedan exit the road to the left side. What types of vehicles that if get removed from the videos, there won't be an accident?", "candidates": ["My vehicle", "Sedan or general car", "Mini van or van", "Sports car or convertible"], "answer": 1, "class": "C", "id": 133}
{"question": "A silver SUV is moving very slowly on a road. A black sedan from the back moving very quickly crashes into the silver SUV. The silver SUV is pushed off the road to the left. Both the silver SUV and the black sedan exit the road to the left side. Was the main cause of the accident due to speeding vehicles?", "candidates": ["No, the involved vehicles also violated other traffic rules", "Yes"], "answer": 1, "class": "C", "id": 134}
{"question": "A silver SUV is moving very slowly on a road. A black sedan from the back moving very quickly crashes into the silver SUV. The silver SUV is pushed off the road to the left. Both the silver SUV and the black sedan exit the road to the left side. Would the accident still happen if the involved vehicles change lane or turn properly?", "candidates": ["Yes, the involved vehicles would still violate traffic rules", "No"], "answer": 1, "class": "C", "id": 135}
{"question": "A silver SUV is moving very slowly on a road. A black sedan from the back moving very quickly crashes into the silver SUV. The silver SUV is pushed off the road to the left. Both the silver SUV and the black sedan exit the road to the left side. Would the accident still happen if the roads have better marking?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes, the involved vehicles would still violate traffic rules"], "answer": 1, "class": "C", "id": 136}
{"question": "A silver SUV is moving very slowly on a road. A black sedan from the back moving very quickly crashes into the silver SUV. The silver SUV is pushed off the road to the left. Both the silver SUV and the black sedan exit the road to the left side. Would the accident still happen if all vehicles drive in their correct lane?", "candidates": ["Yes, the involved vehicles would still violate traffic rules", "No"], "answer": 0, "class": "C", "id": 137}
{"question": "The POV car comes to a rest in the right lane at an intersection with a stop sign. A white sedan in the left lane speeds through the intersection. A red sedan enters the intersection parallelly to the white sedan at a high rate of speed. The red sedan hits the side of white sedan. The red sedan turns towards the left where the red sedan comes to a rest. The white sedan is pushed further back in the same direction where the white sedan is turned around completely before coming to a rest. Would the accident still happen if the involved vehicles move at a lower speed?", "candidates": ["No, the invovled vehicles would have more time to react", "Yes, the involved vehicles would still violate traffic rules"], "answer": 0, "class": "C", "id": 138}
{"question": "The POV car comes to a rest in the right lane at an intersection with a stop sign. A white sedan in the left lane speeds through the intersection. A red sedan enters the intersection parallelly to the white sedan at a high rate of speed. The red sedan hits the side of white sedan. The red sedan turns towards the left where the red sedan comes to a rest. The white sedan is pushed further back in the same direction where the white sedan is turned around completely before coming to a rest. Was the main cause of the accident due to unfavorable weather condition?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, the involved vehicles also violated other traffic rules", "No, the weather is suitable for driving"], "answer": 2, "class": "C", "id": 139}
{"question": "The POV car comes to a rest in the right lane at an intersection with a stop sign. A white sedan in the left lane speeds through the intersection. A red sedan enters the intersection parallelly to the white sedan at a high rate of speed. The red sedan hits the side of white sedan. The red sedan turns towards the left where the red sedan comes to a rest. The white sedan is pushed further back in the same direction where the white sedan is turned around completely before coming to a rest. What types of vehicles that if get removed from the videos, there won't be an accident?", "candidates": ["Trailer truck or heavy truck", "Bicycle or tricycle or non-motor vehicles", "Sedan or general car", "Motorcycle or scooter"], "answer": 2, "class": "C", "id": 140}
{"question": "The POV car comes to a rest in the right lane at an intersection with a stop sign. A white sedan in the left lane speeds through the intersection. A red sedan enters the intersection parallelly to the white sedan at a high rate of speed. The red sedan hits the side of white sedan. The red sedan turns towards the left where the red sedan comes to a rest. The white sedan is pushed further back in the same direction where the white sedan is turned around completely before coming to a rest. Was the main cause of the accident due to speeding vehicles?", "candidates": ["No, the involved vehicles also violated other traffic rules", "Yes"], "answer": 1, "class": "C", "id": 141}
{"question": "The POV car comes to a rest in the right lane at an intersection with a stop sign. A white sedan in the left lane speeds through the intersection. A red sedan enters the intersection parallelly to the white sedan at a high rate of speed. The red sedan hits the side of white sedan. The red sedan turns towards the left where the red sedan comes to a rest. The white sedan is pushed further back in the same direction where the white sedan is turned around completely before coming to a rest. Would the accident still happen if the roads have better marking?", "candidates": ["Yes, the involved vehicles would still violate traffic rules", "No"], "answer": 0, "class": "C", "id": 142}
{"question": "The POV car is driving in the road with a silver SUV behind. The vehicle comes to a stop in the road while the silver SUV continues moving at a slow rate of speed. The silver SUV hits the POV car. The POV car is pushed forwards slightly and continues moving as the silver SUV comes to a rest. Was the main cause of the accident due to improper lane changing or turning?", "candidates": ["No, the involved vehicles also violated other traffic rules", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "C", "id": 143}
{"question": "The POV car is driving in the road with a silver SUV behind. The vehicle comes to a stop in the road while the silver SUV continues moving at a slow rate of speed. The silver SUV hits the POV car. The POV car is pushed forwards slightly and continues moving as the silver SUV comes to a rest. What types of vehicles that if get removed from the videos, there won't be an accident?", "candidates": ["Sports car or convertible", "Pickup truck or light truck", "Bicycle or tricycle or non-motor vehicles", "Suv or cuv"], "answer": 3, "class": "C", "id": 144}
{"question": "The POV car is driving in the road with a silver SUV behind. The vehicle comes to a stop in the road while the silver SUV continues moving at a slow rate of speed. The silver SUV hits the POV car. The POV car is pushed forwards slightly and continues moving as the silver SUV comes to a rest. Would the accident still happen if there are less vehicles on the road?", "candidates": ["Yes, the involved vehicles would still drive recklessly", "No, there would be more space to safely avoid the accident"], "answer": 0, "class": "C", "id": 145}
{"question": "The POV car is driving in the road with a silver SUV behind. The vehicle comes to a stop in the road while the silver SUV continues moving at a slow rate of speed. The silver SUV hits the POV car. The POV car is pushed forwards slightly and continues moving as the silver SUV comes to a rest. Would the accident still happen if the roads have better marking?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes, the involved vehicles would still violate traffic rules"], "answer": 1, "class": "C", "id": 146}
{"question": "The POV car is driving in the road with a silver SUV behind. The vehicle comes to a stop in the road while the silver SUV continues moving at a slow rate of speed. The silver SUV hits the POV car. The POV car is pushed forwards slightly and continues moving as the silver SUV comes to a rest. Was the main cause of the accident due to unfavorable weather condition?", "candidates": ["No, the weather is suitable for driving", "No, the involved vehicles also violated other traffic rules", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "C", "id": 147}
{"question": "Some children are running near some cars that are sitting in the middle lane of a street.  They run from the left side to the right side.  A white van starts down the one-lane road from the left side. A kid running out of the sitting cars is about to be hit by the white van. How will the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["No accident will happen", "Head-on collision", "Side-collision", "The vehicle collided with road infrastructure."], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 148}
{"question": "Some children are running near some cars that are sitting in the middle lane of a street.  They run from the left side to the right side.  A white van starts down the one-lane road from the left side. A kid running out of the sitting cars is about to be hit by the white van. Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["Bus", "Mini van or van", "Motorcycle or scooter", "Suv or cuv"], "answer": 3, "class": "F", "id": 149}
{"question": "Some children are running near some cars that are sitting in the middle lane of a street.  They run from the left side to the right side.  A white van starts down the one-lane road from the left side. A kid running out of the sitting cars is about to be hit by the white van. Are there any vehicles about to change lane or turn?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 150}
{"question": "The POV car is moving through a highway. At the back of the POV car, a red sedan can be seen. The POV car stops suddenly. The red sedan is getting close to the POV car without enough decelerating. Will there be any vehicle(s) rollover crashing?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 151}
{"question": "The POV car is moving through a highway. At the back of the POV car, a red sedan can be seen. The POV car stops suddenly. The red sedan is getting close to the POV car without enough decelerating. Which vehicles are about to cause an accident?", "candidates": ["Pickup truck or light truck", "Mini van or van", "Sedan or general car", "My vehicle"], "answer": 3, "class": "F", "id": 152}
{"question": "The POV car is moving through a highway. At the back of the POV car, a red sedan can be seen. The POV car stops suddenly. The red sedan is getting close to the POV car without enough decelerating. How will the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["Ran-off-road collision", "The vehicle collided with road infrastructure.", "Rear-end collision", "Others"], "answer": 2, "class": "F", "id": 153}
{"question": "The POV car is driving fairly quickly down the road in the right lane. A black sedan in the parking lane starts merging into the right lane in front of the red sedan quickly. The POV car continues traveling at the same speed rate. The POV car sedan gets very close to the black sedan ahead of it with a high speed. Are there any vehicles at a risk of an accident?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 154}
{"question": "The POV car is driving fairly quickly down the road in the right lane. A black sedan in the parking lane starts merging into the right lane in front of the red sedan quickly. The POV car continues traveling at the same speed rate. The POV car sedan gets very close to the black sedan ahead of it with a high speed. Will the vehicles in front able to stop in time before colliding with other vehicles?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 155}
{"question": "The POV car is driving fairly quickly down the road in the right lane. A black sedan in the parking lane starts merging into the right lane in front of the red sedan quickly. The POV car continues traveling at the same speed rate. The POV car sedan gets very close to the black sedan ahead of it with a high speed. Which vehicles are about to cause an accident?", "candidates": ["POV car", "Suv or cuv", "Mini van or van", "Pickup truck or light truck"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 156}
{"question": "The POV car is driving fairly quickly down the road in the right lane. A black sedan in the parking lane starts merging into the right lane in front of the red sedan quickly. The POV car continues traveling at the same speed rate. The POV car sedan gets very close to the black sedan ahead of it with a high speed. How will the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["The vehicle collided with road infrastructure.", "Rear-end collision", "Others", "Ran-off-road collision"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 157}
{"question": "The POV car is driving fairly quickly down the road in the right lane. A black sedan in the parking lane starts merging into the right lane in front of the red sedan quickly. The POV car continues traveling at the same speed rate. The POV car sedan gets very close to the black sedan ahead of it with a high speed. Will there be any vehicle(s) rollover crashing?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 158}
{"question": "The POV car is stopping behind a white hyundai. The POV car suddenly starts to shake heavily and gets a speed forward instantly. ThePOV car almost crashes with white Hyundai ahead. Which vehicles caused an accident?", "candidates": ["The white hyunai", "The POV car", "The car from behind", "The car in the left side"], "answer": 2, "class": "R", "id": 159}
{"question": "The POV car is stopping behind a white hyundai. The POV car suddenly starts to shake heavily and gets a speed forward instantly. ThePOV car almost crashes with white Hyundai ahead. Are there any vehicles about to change lane or turn?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 160}
{"question": "The POV car is stopping behind a white hyundai. The POV car suddenly starts to shake heavily and gets a speed forward instantly. ThePOV car almost crashes with white Hyundai ahead. How did the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["Ran-off-road collision", "Rear-end collision", "Others", "The vehicle collided with road infrastructure."], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 161}
{"question": "The POV car is stopping behind a white hyundai. The POV car suddenly starts to shake heavily and gets a speed forward instantly. ThePOV car almost crashes with white Hyundai ahead. Will there be any vehicle(s) rollover crashing?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 162}
{"question": "Cars are moving at a high speed on a foggy road. A white van and a black suv can be seen. A person starts to run from the middle of the road to the right side of the road. The person ran to the front of the black suv and get really close to the black suv. How will the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["Head-on collision", "Ran-off-road collision", "No accident will happen", "Side-collision"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 163}
{"question": "Cars are moving at a high speed on a foggy road. A white van and a black suv can be seen. A person starts to run from the middle of the road to the right side of the road. The person ran to the front of the black suv and get really close to the black suv. Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["Sports car or convertible", "Suv or cuv", "Motorcycle or scooter", "Sedan or general car"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 164}
{"question": "Cars are moving at a high speed on a foggy road. A white van and a black suv can be seen. A person starts to run from the middle of the road to the right side of the road. The person ran to the front of the black suv and get really close to the black suv. Are there any vehicles at a risk of an accident?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 165}
{"question": "Cars are passing an intersection. An suv and a white car in the left are passing the intersection light. Three cars are driving side by side passing the interesection. Which vehicles are about to drive through the crossroad?", "candidates": ["My vehicle", "Pickup truck or light truck", "Mini van or van", "Motorcycle or scooter"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 166}
{"question": "Cars are passing an intersection. An suv and a white car in the left are passing the intersection light. Three cars are driving side by side passing the interesection. Which vehicles are about to stop?", "candidates": ["Mini van or van", "None", "My vehicle", "Bus"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 167}
{"question": "Cars are passing an intersection. An suv and a white car in the left are passing the intersection light. Three cars are driving side by side passing the interesection. Judging by the speed of the fastest vehicle, will it cause an accident?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 168}
{"question": "Cars are passing an intersection. An suv and a white car in the left are passing the intersection light. Three cars are driving side by side passing the interesection. Which vehicles are about to drive through the crossroad?", "candidates": ["Suv or cuv", "Sedan or general car"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 169}
{"question": "Cars are passing an intersection. An suv and a white car in the left are passing the intersection light. Three cars are driving side by side passing the interesection. Which vehicles are about to turn?", "candidates": ["None", "My vehicle", "Sedan or general car", "Suv or cuv"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 170}
{"question": "Cars are passing an intersection. An suv and a white car in the left are passing the intersection light. Three cars are driving side by side passing the interesection. Which vehicles are about to stop?", "candidates": ["Suv or cuv", "Pickup truck or light truck", "None", "Sedan or general car"], "answer": 2, "class": "F", "id": 171}
{"question": "A vehicle is following a white semi. The vehicle continues to follow a white semi through a green-lighted intersection. After the intersection, a phone pole begins to crash towards the road. A phone pole is falling dangerously close to the road and following vehicle. What accident is about to happen?", "candidates": ["Car collision", "Collision on perdestrains", "Demage by infrastructures"], "answer": 2, "class": "F", "id": 172}
{"question": "The POV car moves to its lane from the opposite one. On its way down the road, the POV car approaches a sedan. The sedan seems to take a turn to the right, however, the sedan suddenly turns back as it was probably going to switch to opposite direction. The sedan is passing the lane just as the POV car is approaching quickly to the sedan. Are there any vehicles at a risk of an accident?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 173}
{"question": "The POV car moves to its lane from the opposite one. On its way down the road, the POV car approaches a sedan. The sedan seems to take a turn to the right, however, the sedan suddenly turns back as it was probably going to switch to opposite direction. The sedan is passing the lane just as the POV car is approaching quickly to the sedan. Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["Motorcycle or scooter", "Bicycle or tricycle or non-motor vehicles", "Trailer truck or heavy truck", "Sedan"], "answer": 3, "class": "F", "id": 174}
{"question": "The POV car moves to its lane from the opposite one. On its way down the road, the POV car approaches a sedan. The sedan seems to take a turn to the right, however, the sedan suddenly turns back as it was probably going to switch to opposite direction. The sedan is passing the lane just as the POV car is approaching quickly to the sedan. How much damage will the vehicle(s) receive after collision?", "candidates": ["Nearly no damage", "Some scratches", "Significant deformation"], "answer": 2, "class": "F", "id": 175}
{"question": "The POV car moves to its lane from the opposite one. On its way down the road, the POV car approaches a sedan. The sedan seems to take a turn to the right, however, the sedan suddenly turns back as it was probably going to switch to opposite direction. The sedan is passing the lane just as the POV car is approaching quickly to the sedan. Are there any vehicles about to change lane or turn?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 176}
{"question": "A motorcycle rider is approaching. The rider loses control of the motorcycle. The rider and motorcycle fall to the ground. The motorcycle rider walks to collect the downed motorcycle. What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Motorcycle / Scooter", "Trailer Truck / Heavy Truck", "Pickup Truck / Light Truck", "Sedan / General Car"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 177}
{"question": "A motorcycle rider is approaching. The rider loses control of the motorcycle. The rider and motorcycle fall to the ground. The motorcycle rider walks to collect the downed motorcycle. Which could be the reason for this accident?", "candidates": ["Vehicle malfunction", "No accident happened", "Improper lane change", "Others"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 178}
{"question": "A motorcycle rider is approaching. The rider loses control of the motorcycle. The rider and motorcycle fall to the ground. The motorcycle rider walks to collect the downed motorcycle. Did an accident happen?", "candidates": ["Yes, the vehicle(s) are in unusual positions", "No, no vehicles receive any damage", "Yes, there are visible damages"], "answer": 2, "class": "R", "id": 179}
{"question": "A suv from the left lane crash on a truck on its right lane. Two vehicles crash each other side by side. How did the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["Side-collision", "Rear-end collision", "Ran-off-road collision", "Head-on collision"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 180}
{"question": "A suv from the left lane crash on a truck on its right lane. Two vehicles crash each other side by side. What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Sports car or convertible", "Motorcycle or scooter", "My vehicle", "Suv or cuv"], "answer": 3, "class": "R", "id": 181}
{"question": "A suv from the left lane crash on a truck on its right lane. Two vehicles crash each other side by side. Did the accident happen when the involved vehicles were changing lane or turning?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 182}
{"question": "A suv from the left lane crash on a truck on its right lane. Two vehicles crash each other side by side. Did an accident happen?", "candidates": ["No, no vehicles receive any damage", "Yes, the vehicle(s) are in unusual positions", "Yes, there are visible damages"], "answer": 2, "class": "R", "id": 183}
{"question": "The POV car is driving very fast in the right-most lane. The POV car collides with a white sedan merging right on its left. The POV car spins and hits a fence on the right and comes to a stop. Which could be the reason for this accident?", "candidates": ["Improper lane change", "Speeding vehicles", "Road safety negligence", "No accident happened"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 184}
{"question": "The POV car is driving very fast in the right-most lane. The POV car collides with a white sedan merging right on its left. The POV car spins and hits a fence on the right and comes to a stop. What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Bus", "My vehicle", "Sedan or general car", "Mini van or van"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 185}
{"question": "The POV car is driving very fast in the right-most lane. The POV car collides with a white sedan merging right on its left. The POV car spins and hits a fence on the right and comes to a stop. Did the accident happen when the involved vehicles were changing lane or turning?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 186}
{"question": "The POV vehicle is parked in a narrow side street. A white scooter quickly approaches the vehicle. The white scooter hits the front of the vehicle. The white scooter recoils from the vehicle. The driver looks dazed. Could the accident be prevented if the involved vehicles check for safety before making a move?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 187}
{"question": "The POV vehicle is parked in a narrow side street. A white scooter quickly approaches the vehicle. The white scooter hits the front of the vehicle. The white scooter recoils from the vehicle. The driver looks dazed. Could the accident be prevented if the road infrastructure is better?", "candidates": ["Yes, better road surface will help", "Yes, larger road will help", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes, better markings will help"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 188}
{"question": "The POV vehicle is parked in a narrow side street. A white scooter quickly approaches the vehicle. The white scooter hits the front of the vehicle. The white scooter recoils from the vehicle. The driver looks dazed. Could the accident be prevented if no vehicles were speeding or driving recklessly?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 189}
{"question": "The POV vehicle is parked in a narrow side street. A white scooter quickly approaches the vehicle. The white scooter hits the front of the vehicle. The white scooter recoils from the vehicle. The driver looks dazed. Which could be the reason for this accident?", "candidates": ["Obstructed view or limited visibility", "Traffic rules violation", "Road safety negligence", "Retrograde vehicles"], "answer": 2, "class": "R", "id": 190}
{"question": "The POV car is travelling on a highway. The POV car is moving through side of road. The POV car has entered grass area. The POV car crashes and turns upside down. Which could be the reason for this accident?", "candidates": ["Retrograde vehicles", "Traffic congestion", "Speeding vehicles", "Road safety negligence"], "answer": 3, "class": "R", "id": 191}
{"question": "The POV car is travelling on a highway. The POV car is moving through side of road. The POV car has entered grass area. The POV car crashes and turns upside down. What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Bus", "Mini van or van", "My vehicle", "Trailer truck or heavy truck"], "answer": 2, "class": "R", "id": 192}
{"question": "The POV car is travelling on a highway. The POV car is moving through side of road. The POV car has entered grass area. The POV car crashes and turns upside down. What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Motorcycle or scooter", "My vehicle", "Sedan or general car", "Suv or cuv"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 193}
{"question": "The POV car is driving forwards at a fairly high rate in the left lane under a bridge. A white compact car suddenly appears in the view of the POV car. The white compact car proceeds to enter the main road from the left fork of the road. The white compact car crashes into the POV car's side. The POV car slows before staying still in the middle lane. What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["SUV / CUV", "Trailer Truck / Heavy Truck", "Sedan / General Car", "Pickup Truck / Light Truck"], "answer": 2, "class": "R", "id": 194}
{"question": "The POV car is driving forwards at a fairly high rate in the left lane under a bridge. A white compact car suddenly appears in the view of the POV car. The white compact car proceeds to enter the main road from the left fork of the road. The white compact car crashes into the POV car's side. The POV car slows before staying still in the middle lane. Which could be the reason for this accident?", "candidates": ["Improper lane change", "Retrograde vehicles", "Traffic rules violation", "Obstructed view or limited visibility"], "answer": 3, "class": "R", "id": 195}
{"question": "The POV car is driving forwards at a fairly high rate in the left lane under a bridge. A white compact car suddenly appears in the view of the POV car. The white compact car proceeds to enter the main road from the left fork of the road. The white compact car crashes into the POV car's side. The POV car slows before staying still in the middle lane. How did the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["Others", "Rear-end collision", "The vehicle collided with road infrastructure.", "Side-collision"], "answer": 3, "class": "R", "id": 196}
{"question": "The POV car is driving forwards at a fairly high rate in the left lane under a bridge. A white compact car suddenly appears in the view of the POV car. The white compact car proceeds to enter the main road from the left fork of the road. The white compact car crashes into the POV car's side. The POV car slows before staying still in the middle lane. What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Bicycle / Tricycle / Non-motor Vehicles", "Others", "Motorcycle / Scooter", "My vehicle"], "answer": 3, "class": "R", "id": 197}
{"question": "The POV car is being rocked as if colliding. The POV car car is rocked. There are black parts flying in front of the car. There are black plastic parts in front of the POV car. What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Motorcycle or scooter", "POV car", "Sedan or general car", "Mini van or van"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 198}
{"question": "The POV car is being rocked as if colliding. The POV car car is rocked. There are black parts flying in front of the car. There are black plastic parts in front of the POV car. How many vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["One", "More than five", "Two", "None"], "answer": 2, "class": "R", "id": 199}
{"question": "The POV car is being rocked as if colliding. The POV car car is rocked. There are black parts flying in front of the car. There are black plastic parts in front of the POV car. Did the accident happen when the involved vehicles were speeding?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes, the invovled vehicles were badly damaged", "Yes, the involved vehicles continued to speed away"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 200}
{"question": "The POV car is being rocked as if colliding. The POV car car is rocked. There are black parts flying in front of the car. There are black plastic parts in front of the POV car. Did the accident happen when the involved vehicles were changing lane or turning?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 201}
{"question": "The POV car is being rocked as if colliding. The POV car car is rocked. There are black parts flying in front of the car. There are black plastic parts in front of the POV car. Did an accident happen?", "candidates": ["Yes, the vehicle(s) are in unusual positions", "No, no vehicles receive any damage", "Yes, there are visible damages"], "answer": 2, "class": "R", "id": 202}
{"question": "The POV car is driving fast in the right lane of the road.  The POV car spins out of control before coming to a rest facing the opposite direction. A black sedan remains resting in the back of the POV car with its dumper off. What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Sedan or general car", "Sports car or convertible", "Motorcycle or scooter", "Others"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 203}
{"question": "The POV car is driving fast in the right lane of the road.  The POV car spins out of control before coming to a rest facing the opposite direction. A black sedan remains resting in the back of the POV car with its dumper off. What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["My vehicle", "Trailer truck or heavy truck", "Mini van or van", "Suv or cuv"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 204}
{"question": "The POV car is driving fast in the right lane of the road.  The POV car spins out of control before coming to a rest facing the opposite direction. A black sedan remains resting in the back of the POV car with its dumper off. How did the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["The vehicle collided with road infrastructure.", "Side-collision", "Others", "Rear-end collision"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 205}
{"question": "The POV car is driving fast in the right lane of the road.  The POV car spins out of control before coming to a rest facing the opposite direction. A black sedan remains resting in the back of the POV car with its dumper off. How fast did the vehicles involved in the accident move before they crash, based on the speed of the fastest one?", "candidates": ["Slower than other vehicles", "Faster than other vehicles", "Roughly the same as other vehicles"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 206}
{"question": "The POV car is driving fast in the right lane of the road.  The POV car spins out of control before coming to a rest facing the opposite direction. A black sedan remains resting in the back of the POV car with its dumper off. Did an accident happen?", "candidates": ["No, no vehicles receive any damage", "Yes, there are visible damages"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 207}
{"question": "The POV car is driving fast in the right lane of the road.  The POV car spins out of control before coming to a rest facing the opposite direction. A black sedan remains resting in the back of the POV car with its dumper off. Did the accident happen when the involved vehicles were speeding?", "candidates": ["Yes, the involved vehicles continued to speed away", "Yes, the invovled vehicles were badly damaged", "No"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 208}
{"question": "The POV car is veering across the median of the road. The POV car drives across the median and hits a pole.  The POV car hits a speeding black SUV after it cross the median of the road. The black SUV flips around. Which could be the reason for this accident?", "candidates": ["Improper lane change", "Road safety negligence", "Obstructed view or limited visibility", "No accident happened"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 209}
{"question": "The POV car is veering across the median of the road. The POV car drives across the median and hits a pole.  The POV car hits a speeding black SUV after it cross the median of the road. The black SUV flips around. What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["My vehicle", "Others", "Trailer truck or heavy truck", "Bus"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 210}
{"question": "A red sedan is slwoly attempting to turn into the right lane of the road from the right. A second red sedan quickly coming close to the first red sedan. The second red sedan crashes the side of the first red sedan. The two red sedans remain still in the road.  Which could be the reason for this accident?", "candidates": ["Traffic rules violation", "Road safety negligence", "No accident happened", "Others"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 211}
{"question": "A red sedan is slwoly attempting to turn into the right lane of the road from the right. A second red sedan quickly coming close to the first red sedan. The second red sedan crashes the side of the first red sedan. The two red sedans remain still in the road.  How did the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["Rear-end collision", "Others", "Side-collision", "The vehicle collided with road infrastructure."], "answer": 2, "class": "R", "id": 212}
{"question": "A red sedan is slwoly attempting to turn into the right lane of the road from the right. A second red sedan quickly coming close to the first red sedan. The second red sedan crashes the side of the first red sedan. The two red sedans remain still in the road.  What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Bus", "general car", "Pickup truck or light truck", "Mini van or van"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 213}
{"question": "A red sedan is slwoly attempting to turn into the right lane of the road from the right. A second red sedan quickly coming close to the first red sedan. The second red sedan crashes the side of the first red sedan. The two red sedans remain still in the road.  Which could be the reason for this accident?", "candidates": ["Obstructed view or limited visibility", "Speeding vehicles", "Improper lane change", "Traffic light violation"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 214}
{"question": "A silver sedan on the left lane of the road is driving fast. The sliver sedan gets extremely close to a stopped burgundy sedan in front. The silver sedan bumps the rear of burgundy sedan at moderate speed. Both burgundy sedan and silver sedan stop. Which could be the reason for this accident?", "candidates": ["No accident happened", "Traffic congestion", "Traffic rules violation", "Road safety negligence"], "answer": 3, "class": "R", "id": 215}
{"question": "A silver sedan on the left lane of the road is driving fast. The sliver sedan gets extremely close to a stopped burgundy sedan in front. The silver sedan bumps the rear of burgundy sedan at moderate speed. Both burgundy sedan and silver sedan stop. How did the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["The vehicle collided with road infrastructure.", "Rear-end collision", "Others", "Side-collision"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 216}
{"question": "A silver sedan on the left lane of the road is driving fast. The sliver sedan gets extremely close to a stopped burgundy sedan in front. The silver sedan bumps the rear of burgundy sedan at moderate speed. Both burgundy sedan and silver sedan stop. What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Bicycle / Tricycle / Non-motor Vehicles", "Sedan / General Car", "Bus", "Trailer Truck / Heavy Truck"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 217}
{"question": "The POV car is driving down a wet road. The road is very slippery due to the rain. Traffic is fairly light. A truck hits the rare of a speeding black suv. The black suv loses its balance and slipped to the opposite lane. The black suv hit another black sedan in the opposite lane. The black sedan spins and reverse out of the road. Would the accident still happen if the involved vehicles move at a lower speed?", "candidates": ["No, the invovled vehicles would not lose control", "Yes, the involved vehicles would still violate traffic rules"], "answer": 0, "class": "C", "id": 218}
{"question": "The POV car is driving down a wet road. The road is very slippery due to the rain. Traffic is fairly light. A truck hits the rare of a speeding black suv. The black suv loses its balance and slipped to the opposite lane. The black suv hit another black sedan in the opposite lane. The black sedan spins and reverse out of the road. Would the accident still happen if the involved vehicles change lane or turn properly?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": 0, "class": "C", "id": 219}
{"question": "The POV car is driving down a wet road. The road is very slippery due to the rain. Traffic is fairly light. A truck hits the rare of a speeding black suv. The black suv loses its balance and slipped to the opposite lane. The black suv hit another black sedan in the opposite lane. The black sedan spins and reverse out of the road. What types of vehicles that if get removed from the videos, there won't be an accident?", "candidates": ["My vehicle", "Motorcycle or scooter", "Suv or cuv", "Bicycle or tricycle or non-motor vehicles"], "answer": 2, "class": "C", "id": 220}
{"question": "The POV car is driving down a wet road. The road is very slippery due to the rain. Traffic is fairly light. A truck hits the rare of a speeding black suv. The black suv loses its balance and slipped to the opposite lane. The black suv hit another black sedan in the opposite lane. The black sedan spins and reverse out of the road. Was the main cause of the accident due to unfavorable weather condition?", "candidates": ["No, the weather is suitable for driving", "Yes", "No, the involved vehicles also violated other traffic rules"], "answer": 1, "class": "C", "id": 221}
{"question": "The POV car is going slowly behind a SUV. The POV car's camera view suddenly starts to shake and speed up. The POV car collide with the rear of the SUV.  What types of vehicles that if get removed from the videos, there won't be an accident?", "candidates": ["Sedan or general car", "Bicycle or tricycle or non-motor vehicles", "Motorcycle or scooter", "My vehicle"], "answer": 3, "class": "C", "id": 222}
{"question": "The POV car is going slowly behind a SUV. The POV car's camera view suddenly starts to shake and speed up. The POV car collide with the rear of the SUV.  Was the main cause of the accident due to improper lane changing or turning?", "candidates": ["No, the involved vehicles also violated other traffic rules", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "C", "id": 223}
{"question": "The POV car is going slowly behind a SUV. The POV car's camera view suddenly starts to shake and speed up. The POV car collide with the rear of the SUV.  Would the accident still happen if all vehicles drive in their correct lane?", "candidates": ["Yes, the involved vehicles would still violate traffic rules", "No"], "answer": 0, "class": "C", "id": 224}
{"question": "The POV car is going slowly behind a SUV. The POV car's camera view suddenly starts to shake and speed up. The POV car collide with the rear of the SUV.  Was the main cause of the accident due to speeding vehicles?", "candidates": ["No, the involved vehicles also violated other traffic rules", "Yes"], "answer": 1, "class": "C", "id": 225}
{"question": "The POV car is going slowly behind a SUV. The POV car's camera view suddenly starts to shake and speed up. The POV car collide with the rear of the SUV.  Would the accident still happen if the involved vehicles change lane or turn properly?", "candidates": ["Yes, the involved vehicles would still violate traffic rules", "No"], "answer": 0, "class": "C", "id": 226}
{"question": "The POV car moving slowly towards traffic lights spot. An ambulance SUV drives fast from the left road. When turning, it hits the traffic light post in the corner, demolishing it. The SUV then continues with the turn. The SUV leaves after passing beside the POV car. Could the accident be prevented if all vehicles drive in the correct direction?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 227}
{"question": "The POV car moving slowly towards traffic lights spot. An ambulance SUV drives fast from the left road. When turning, it hits the traffic light post in the corner, demolishing it. The SUV then continues with the turn. The SUV leaves after passing beside the POV car. Could the accident be prevented if a convex mirror is installed at the turning point?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes, there would be no obstructed views"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 228}
{"question": "The POV car moving slowly towards traffic lights spot. An ambulance SUV drives fast from the left road. When turning, it hits the traffic light post in the corner, demolishing it. The SUV then continues with the turn. The SUV leaves after passing beside the POV car. Could any involved vehicles stop in time to prevent the accident?", "candidates": ["No, there was no time to react", "Yes, there was enough time to react"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 229}
{"question": "The POV car moving slowly towards traffic lights spot. An ambulance SUV drives fast from the left road. When turning, it hits the traffic light post in the corner, demolishing it. The SUV then continues with the turn. The SUV leaves after passing beside the POV car. Could the accident be prevented if the involved vehicles check for safety before making a move?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 230}
{"question": "The POV car is moving through a busy highway. The traffic in front of the POV suddenly stopped. The POV car is attempting to move to the next left line. But the POV car is hit by the car behind. The POV car acclerated into the black car. Could the accident be prevented if the involved vehicles change lane or turn properly?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 231}
{"question": "The POV car is moving through a busy highway. The traffic in front of the POV suddenly stopped. The POV car is attempting to move to the next left line. But the POV car is hit by the car behind. The POV car acclerated into the black car. Could the accident be prevented if all vehicles drive in the correct direction?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 232}
{"question": "The POV car is moving through a busy highway. The traffic in front of the POV suddenly stopped. The POV car is attempting to move to the next left line. But the POV car is hit by the car behind. The POV car acclerated into the black car. Could the accident be prevented if all vehicles keep a safe distance away from one another?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 233}
{"question": "The POV car is moving through a busy highway. The traffic in front of the POV suddenly stopped. The POV car is attempting to move to the next left line. But the POV car is hit by the car behind. The POV car acclerated into the black car. Could the accident be prevented if the involved vehicles check for safety before making a move?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 234}
{"question": "The POV car is moving through a busy highway. The traffic in front of the POV suddenly stopped. The POV car is attempting to move to the next left line. But the POV car is hit by the car behind. The POV car acclerated into the black car. What is the main reason of the accident?", "candidates": ["Sudden brake of the front car", "Improper lane change", "Traffic light violation"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 235}
{"question": "A red truck is in the distance from the POV car on the road. The POV car stops. The red truck gets close to the POV car without decelerating. The red truck hits the POV car from behind and rolls back.  Could the accident be prevented if the involved vehicles check for safety before making a move?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 236}
{"question": "A red truck is in the distance from the POV car on the road. The POV car stops. The red truck gets close to the POV car without decelerating. The red truck hits the POV car from behind and rolls back.  Could the accident be prevented if all vehicles drive in the correct direction?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 237}
{"question": "A red truck is in the distance from the POV car on the road. The POV car stops. The red truck gets close to the POV car without decelerating. The red truck hits the POV car from behind and rolls back.  Could the accident be prevented if the involved vehicles change lane or turn properly?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 238}
{"question": "A red truck is in the distance from the POV car on the road. The POV car stops. The red truck gets close to the POV car without decelerating. The red truck hits the POV car from behind and rolls back.  Could the accident be prevented if all vehicles keep a safe distance away from one another?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 239}
{"question": "A red truck is in the distance from the POV car on the road. The POV car stops. The red truck gets close to the POV car without decelerating. The red truck hits the POV car from behind and rolls back.  Could the accident be prevented if the including drivers pay more attention on the road?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 240}
{"question": "The POV car is moving forwards at a fairly high rate of speed in the right lane. The POV car quickly merges into the left lane. The POV car approaches an intersection without traffic that a small black sedan is slowly entering. The POV car continues at the same speed and crashes the side of the small black sedan. Both the same black sedan and the POV car spin out of the road and crash into a stop sign before coming to a rest. Could the accident be prevented if no vehicles make sudden movements?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 241}
{"question": "The POV car is moving forwards at a fairly high rate of speed in the right lane. The POV car quickly merges into the left lane. The POV car approaches an intersection without traffic that a small black sedan is slowly entering. The POV car continues at the same speed and crashes the side of the small black sedan. Both the same black sedan and the POV car spin out of the road and crash into a stop sign before coming to a rest. Could the accident be prevented if the involved vehicles change lane or turn properly?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 242}
{"question": "The POV car is moving forwards at a fairly high rate of speed in the right lane. The POV car quickly merges into the left lane. The POV car approaches an intersection without traffic that a small black sedan is slowly entering. The POV car continues at the same speed and crashes the side of the small black sedan. Both the same black sedan and the POV car spin out of the road and crash into a stop sign before coming to a rest. Could the accident be prevented if a convex mirror is installed at the turning point?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes, there would be no obstructed views"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 243}
{"question": "The POV car is moving forwards at a fairly high rate of speed in the right lane. The POV car quickly merges into the left lane. The POV car approaches an intersection without traffic that a small black sedan is slowly entering. The POV car continues at the same speed and crashes the side of the small black sedan. Both the same black sedan and the POV car spin out of the road and crash into a stop sign before coming to a rest. Could the accident be prevented if the cars check for safety before making a move?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 244}
{"question": "The road is wet.  The POV car is driving fast in the second left-most lane. A white truck coming from the right road cuts the POV car's road off. The POV car quickly swerves left and hits the black car in the left most lane. The POV car hit the black car and the POV car's hood pops open. Could the accident be prevented if all vehicles keep a safe distance away from one another?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 245}
{"question": "The road is wet.  The POV car is driving fast in the second left-most lane. A white truck coming from the right road cuts the POV car's road off. The POV car quickly swerves left and hits the black car in the left most lane. The POV car hit the black car and the POV car's hood pops open. Could the accident be prevented if no vehicles were speeding or driving recklessly?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 246}
{"question": "The road is wet.  The POV car is driving fast in the second left-most lane. A white truck coming from the right road cuts the POV car's road off. The POV car quickly swerves left and hits the black car in the left most lane. The POV car hit the black car and the POV car's hood pops open. Is the weather is suitable for driving?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 247}
{"question": "The road is wet.  The POV car is driving fast in the second left-most lane. A white truck coming from the right road cuts the POV car's road off. The POV car quickly swerves left and hits the black car in the left most lane. The POV car hit the black car and the POV car's hood pops open. Could the accident be prevented if all vehicles appear in the correct position?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No, that was not the main cause of the accident"], "answer": 0, "class": "I", "id": 248}
{"question": "A pedestrian carrying an orange bag starts crossing the street. As she walks from right to left across the crosswalk, the POV car stops behind the perdestrain. The POV car is about to make a left turn after the pedestrain pass. Which vehicles are about to stop?", "candidates": ["Bus", "Mini van or van", "None", "My vehicle"], "answer": 3, "class": "F", "id": 249}
{"question": "A pedestrian carrying an orange bag starts crossing the street. As she walks from right to left across the crosswalk, the POV car stops behind the perdestrain. The POV car is about to make a left turn after the pedestrain pass. Are there any vehicles going to drive through a crossroad?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 250}
{"question": "A pedestrian carrying an orange bag starts crossing the street. As she walks from right to left across the crosswalk, the POV car stops behind the perdestrain. The POV car is about to make a left turn after the pedestrain pass. Are there any vehicles about to turn?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 251}
{"question": "Traffic on four-lane highway is stopping abruptly. A blue sedan in the left lane stops abruptly with the traffic. A white sedan in the back of the blue sedan doesn't decelerate and get closer quickly to the white sedan. Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["Pickup truck or light truck", "Sedan or general car", "Mini van or van", "Motorcycle or scooter"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 252}
{"question": "Traffic on four-lane highway is stopping abruptly. A blue sedan in the left lane stops abruptly with the traffic. A white sedan in the back of the blue sedan doesn't decelerate and get closer quickly to the white sedan. Will all vehicles able to safely avoid an accident?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 253}
{"question": "Traffic on four-lane highway is stopping abruptly. A blue sedan in the left lane stops abruptly with the traffic. A white sedan in the back of the blue sedan doesn't decelerate and get closer quickly to the white sedan. How many vehicles will be involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["None", "Two", "Three to five", "One"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 254}
{"question": "The POV car is driving down an empty highway. A white sedan comes from the opposite direction straight ahead of the POV car. The white sedan comes near the POV car. The POV car and the White sedan both try to merge right, to avoid an accident. How much damage will the vehicle(s) receive after collision?", "candidates": ["Some scratches", "Nearly no damage", "Significant deformation"], "answer": 2, "class": "F", "id": 255}
{"question": "The POV car is driving down an empty highway. A white sedan comes from the opposite direction straight ahead of the POV car. The white sedan comes near the POV car. The POV car and the White sedan both try to merge right, to avoid an accident. Are there any vehicles at a risk of an accident?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 256}
{"question": "The POV car is driving down an empty highway. A white sedan comes from the opposite direction straight ahead of the POV car. The white sedan comes near the POV car. The POV car and the White sedan both try to merge right, to avoid an accident. Judging by the speed of the fastest vehicle, will it cause an accident?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 257}
{"question": "The POV car is driving down an empty highway. A white sedan comes from the opposite direction straight ahead of the POV car. The white sedan comes near the POV car. The POV car and the White sedan both try to merge right, to avoid an accident. How many vehicles will be involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Two", "Three to five", "One", "None"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 258}
{"question": "The POV car is driving in the second right turn lane. A white car in front suddenly merge from the right lane to the POV car's lane. The white car cuts off The POV car. The POV car is close to hitting the white car. Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["Pickup Truck / Light Truck", "Mini Van / Van", "My vehicle", "Bus"], "answer": 2, "class": "F", "id": 259}
{"question": "The POV car is driving in the second right turn lane. A white car in front suddenly merge from the right lane to the POV car's lane. The white car cuts off The POV car. The POV car is close to hitting the white car. How will the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["Others", "Head-on collision", "No accident will happen", "Side-collision"], "answer": 3, "class": "F", "id": 260}
{"question": "The POV car is driving in the second right turn lane. A white car in front suddenly merge from the right lane to the POV car's lane. The white car cuts off The POV car. The POV car is close to hitting the white car. Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["Motorcycle / Scooter", "SUV / CUV", "Trailer Truck / Heavy Truck", "Sedan / General Car"], "answer": 3, "class": "F", "id": 261}
{"question": "The POV car is driving in the second right turn lane. A white car in front suddenly merge from the right lane to the POV car's lane. The white car cuts off The POV car. The POV car is close to hitting the white car. Will all vehicles able to safely avoid an accident?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 262}
{"question": "A scooter is moving forward at a high speed. All the vehicles in front are stopped. The scooter is trying to stop. Scooter is about to hit the SUV in front. Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["Bicycle or tricycle or non-motor vehicles", "Sports car or convertible", "Motorcycle or scooter", "Suv or cuv"], "answer": 2, "class": "F", "id": 263}
{"question": "A scooter is moving forward at a high speed. All the vehicles in front are stopped. The scooter is trying to stop. Scooter is about to hit the SUV in front. How will the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["Rear-end collision", "Others", "Head-on collision", "The vehicle collided with road infrastructure."], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 264}
{"question": "A scooter is moving forward at a high speed. All the vehicles in front are stopped. The scooter is trying to stop. Scooter is about to hit the SUV in front. Judging by the speed of my vehicle, will my vehicle crash into other vehicles?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 265}
{"question": "A black sedan speeding down the road in somewhat busy traffic. The black sedan reaches an intersection at high speed, while  a white SUV is getting in its path from the left. Thr black sedan is about to ram into the side of the white SUV. Will there be any vehicle(s) rollover crashing?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 266}
{"question": "A black sedan speeding down the road in somewhat busy traffic. The black sedan reaches an intersection at high speed, while  a white SUV is getting in its path from the left. Thr black sedan is about to ram into the side of the white SUV. Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["Sports car or convertible", "Suv or cuv", "Bicycle or tricycle or non-motor vehicles", "Bus"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 267}
{"question": "A black sedan speeding down the road in somewhat busy traffic. The black sedan reaches an intersection at high speed, while  a white SUV is getting in its path from the left. Thr black sedan is about to ram into the side of the white SUV. Judging by the speed of the fastest vehicle, will it cause an accident?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 268}
{"question": "The POV car is moving through a busy T junction and trying to turn left. A black suv is coming from left. A white sedan is coming from right. The white sedan is trying to turn left. The white sedan cuts the road of the POV car. The POV car crashs the side of the white sedan. How will the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["Side-collision", "No accident will happen", "The vehicle collided with road infrastructure.", "Ran-off-road collision"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 269}
{"question": "The POV car is moving through a busy T junction and trying to turn left. A black suv is coming from left. A white sedan is coming from right. The white sedan is trying to turn left. The white sedan cuts the road of the POV car. The POV car crashs the side of the white sedan. Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["SUV / CUV", "Mini Van / Van", "Motorcycle / Scooter", "Sedan / General Car"], "answer": 3, "class": "F", "id": 270}
{"question": "The POV car is moving through a busy T junction and trying to turn left. A black suv is coming from left. A white sedan is coming from right. The white sedan is trying to turn left. The white sedan cuts the road of the POV car. The POV car crashs the side of the white sedan. Are there any vehicles at a risk of an accident?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 271}
{"question": "The POV car is approaching an intersection. The POV car is driving slowly to the left turn lane. The POV car passes a white car on the right. The POV car approaches the left turn lane and waits for turning. Which vehicles are about to turn?", "candidates": ["Sedan or general car", "Motorcycle or scooter", "Suv or cuv", "My vehicle"], "answer": 3, "class": "F", "id": 272}
{"question": "The POV car is approaching an intersection. The POV car is driving slowly to the left turn lane. The POV car passes a white car on the right. The POV car approaches the left turn lane and waits for turning. Are there any vehicles going to make a stop?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 273}
{"question": "The POV car is approaching an intersection. The POV car is driving slowly to the left turn lane. The POV car passes a white car on the right. The POV car approaches the left turn lane and waits for turning. Which vehicles are about to drive through the crossroad?", "candidates": ["Mini van or van", "Suv or cuv", "My vehicle", "Motorcycle or scooter"], "answer": 2, "class": "F", "id": 274}
{"question": "A navy sedan and a burgundy SUV are crossing an intersection from different paths. The navy sedan is coming from the opposite direction of the POV car's direction. The burgundy SUV is coming from the left side ofthe intersection. The navy sedan is crossing the intersection at low speed, while the burgundy SUV is approaching the intersection from the side at a rapid speed. The burgundy SUV is about to ram into the navy sedan. How much damage will the vehicle(s) receive after collision?", "candidates": ["Some scratches", "Significant deformation", "Nearly no damage"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 275}
{"question": "A navy sedan and a burgundy SUV are crossing an intersection from different paths. The navy sedan is coming from the opposite direction of the POV car's direction. The burgundy SUV is coming from the left side ofthe intersection. The navy sedan is crossing the intersection at low speed, while the burgundy SUV is approaching the intersection from the side at a rapid speed. The burgundy SUV is about to ram into the navy sedan. How many vehicles will be involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["One", "Three to five", "Two", "None"], "answer": 2, "class": "F", "id": 276}
{"question": "A navy sedan and a burgundy SUV are crossing an intersection from different paths. The navy sedan is coming from the opposite direction of the POV car's direction. The burgundy SUV is coming from the left side ofthe intersection. The navy sedan is crossing the intersection at low speed, while the burgundy SUV is approaching the intersection from the side at a rapid speed. The burgundy SUV is about to ram into the navy sedan. Judging by the speed of the fastest vehicle, will it cause an accident?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 277}
{"question": "A navy sedan and a burgundy SUV are crossing an intersection from different paths. The navy sedan is coming from the opposite direction of the POV car's direction. The burgundy SUV is coming from the left side ofthe intersection. The navy sedan is crossing the intersection at low speed, while the burgundy SUV is approaching the intersection from the side at a rapid speed. The burgundy SUV is about to ram into the navy sedan. How will the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["Others", "Side-collision", "Ran-off-road collision", "Rear-end collision"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 278}
{"question": "A brown sedan is being followed by the POV vehicle in the left lane. A white SUV is in the right lane. The white SUV begins to merge into the left lane. The POV vehicle must brake in order not to graze the white SUV. The white SUV continues to merge into the vehicle's lane. The POV vehicle doesn't drake on time. Will there be any vehicle(s) rollover crashing?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 279}
{"question": "A brown sedan is being followed by the POV vehicle in the left lane. A white SUV is in the right lane. The white SUV begins to merge into the left lane. The POV vehicle must brake in order not to graze the white SUV. The white SUV continues to merge into the vehicle's lane. The POV vehicle doesn't drake on time. How will the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["Others", "Ran-off-road collision", "Side-collision", "The vehicle collided with road infrastructure."], "answer": 2, "class": "F", "id": 280}
{"question": "A brown sedan is being followed by the POV vehicle in the left lane. A white SUV is in the right lane. The white SUV begins to merge into the left lane. The POV vehicle must brake in order not to graze the white SUV. The white SUV continues to merge into the vehicle's lane. The POV vehicle doesn't drake on time. Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["My vehicle", "Trailer Truck / Heavy Truck", "Pickup Truck / Light Truck", "Motorcycle / Scooter"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 281}
{"question": "Approaching an intersection, a white sedan is on a left-turn lane, while another white sedan is slightly behind and on a forward lane. The white sedan suddenly tries to squeeze to the right just in front of the the second white sedan, trying to get into the driving lane in the last moment. The white sedan is about to get hit by the second white sedan. Are there any vehicles at a risk of an accident?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 282}
{"question": "Approaching an intersection, a white sedan is on a left-turn lane, while another white sedan is slightly behind and on a forward lane. The white sedan suddenly tries to squeeze to the right just in front of the the second white sedan, trying to get into the driving lane in the last moment. The white sedan is about to get hit by the second white sedan. Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["Sedan / General Car", "Bus", "Motorcycle / Scooter", "Trailer Truck / Heavy Truck"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 283}
{"question": "Approaching an intersection, a white sedan is on a left-turn lane, while another white sedan is slightly behind and on a forward lane. The white sedan suddenly tries to squeeze to the right just in front of the the second white sedan, trying to get into the driving lane in the last moment. The white sedan is about to get hit by the second white sedan. How will the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["Head-on collision", "Side-collision", "The vehicle collided with road infrastructure.", "Rear-end collision"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 284}
{"question": "There is a road with several scooters driving in the bike lane. There is a scooter approaching the intersection to cross. A white van in front of the scooter begins making a right turn at an intersection. The scooter hits the side of the white van. How will the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["Ran-off-road collision", "No accident will happen", "Others", "Side-collision"], "answer": 3, "class": "F", "id": 285}
{"question": "There is a road with several scooters driving in the bike lane. There is a scooter approaching the intersection to cross. A white van in front of the scooter begins making a right turn at an intersection. The scooter hits the side of the white van. Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["My vehicle", "Mini van or van", "Bicycle or tricycle or non-motor vehicles", "Motorcycle or scooter"], "answer": 3, "class": "F", "id": 286}
{"question": "The POV car is motionless, waiting in front of a highway junction. A black sedan, a scooter, and a red sedan cross by. The POV car takes a free right turn. The POV car merges onto the right highway. Which vehicles are about to stop?", "candidates": ["Sedan or general car", "My vehicle", "Pickup truck or light truck", "None"], "answer": 3, "class": "F", "id": 287}
{"question": "The POV car is motionless, waiting in front of a highway junction. A black sedan, a scooter, and a red sedan cross by. The POV car takes a free right turn. The POV car merges onto the right highway. Are there any vehicles about to turn?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 288}
{"question": "The POV car is motionless, waiting in front of a highway junction. A black sedan, a scooter, and a red sedan cross by. The POV car takes a free right turn. The POV car merges onto the right highway. Which vehicles are about to turn?", "candidates": ["My vehicle", "Sedan or general car", "Pickup truck or light truck", "Motorcycle or scooter"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 289}
{"question": "The POV car is driving down a residential road. A black sedan is approaching fast from the opposite lane. The POV car begins to turn left into the path of the black sedan. The black sedan get very close to the POV car in a high speed. Are there any vehicles at a risk of an accident?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 290}
{"question": "The POV car is driving down a residential road. A black sedan is approaching fast from the opposite lane. The POV car begins to turn left into the path of the black sedan. The black sedan get very close to the POV car in a high speed. Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["Motorcycle / Scooter", "Trailer Truck / Heavy Truck", "Bus", "Sedan / General Car"], "answer": 3, "class": "F", "id": 291}
{"question": "The POV car is driving down a residential road. A black sedan is approaching fast from the opposite lane. The POV car begins to turn left into the path of the black sedan. The black sedan get very close to the POV car in a high speed. Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["My vehicle", "Pickup Truck / Light Truck", "SUV / CUV", "Mini Van / Van"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 292}
{"question": "The POV car is driving down a residential road. A black sedan is approaching fast from the opposite lane. The POV car begins to turn left into the path of the black sedan. The black sedan get very close to the POV car in a high speed. How will the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["Others", "Rear-end collision", "Head-on collision", "Side-collision"], "answer": 3, "class": "F", "id": 293}
{"question": "The POV car driving down the multi-lane road during a relatively busy traffic. The POV car slows down on the signs of congested traffic ahead. Another white sedan merges to the POV car's lane immediately. The POV car is pushed to the right. How much damage will the vehicle(s) receive after collision?", "candidates": ["Significant deformation", "Some scratches", "Nearly no damage"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 294}
{"question": "The POV car driving down the multi-lane road during a relatively busy traffic. The POV car slows down on the signs of congested traffic ahead. Another white sedan merges to the POV car's lane immediately. The POV car is pushed to the right. Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["Sedan or general car", "My vehicle", "Sports car or convertible", "Motorcycle or scooter"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 295}
{"question": "The POV car driving down the multi-lane road during a relatively busy traffic. The POV car slows down on the signs of congested traffic ahead. Another white sedan merges to the POV car's lane immediately. The POV car is pushed to the right. Are there any vehicles at a risk of an accident?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 296}
{"question": "On a busy road, a sedan is driving just next to a bus. Both sedan and the bus slow down near what appears as an intersection. Both the sedan and the bus are turning to the left. While turning, the bus gets a bit ahead of the sedan. The sedan gets dangerously close to the bus and it looks like it is about to collide with it. How will the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["Rear-end collision", "Head-on collision", "Side-collision", "The vehicle collided with road infrastructure."], "answer": 2, "class": "F", "id": 297}
{"question": "On a busy road, a sedan is driving just next to a bus. Both sedan and the bus slow down near what appears as an intersection. Both the sedan and the bus are turning to the left. While turning, the bus gets a bit ahead of the sedan. The sedan gets dangerously close to the bus and it looks like it is about to collide with it. How much damage will the vehicle(s) receive after collision?", "candidates": ["Nearly no damage", "Some scratches", "Significant deformation"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 298}
{"question": "On a busy road, a sedan is driving just next to a bus. Both sedan and the bus slow down near what appears as an intersection. Both the sedan and the bus are turning to the left. While turning, the bus gets a bit ahead of the sedan. The sedan gets dangerously close to the bus and it looks like it is about to collide with it. Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["Trailer Truck / Heavy Truck", "Sedan / General Car", "Motorcycle / Scooter", "Pickup Truck / Light Truck"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 299}
{"question": "On a busy road, a sedan is driving just next to a bus. Both sedan and the bus slow down near what appears as an intersection. Both the sedan and the bus are turning to the left. While turning, the bus gets a bit ahead of the sedan. The sedan gets dangerously close to the bus and it looks like it is about to collide with it. Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["Mini Van / Van", "Bus", "My vehicle", "SUV / CUV"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 300}
{"question": "The POV car is going down the middle of a three land road. As it comes to an intersection a gray oncoming sedan turns left followed by a blue sedan wherewith the car still going through the intersection. The POV car and the blue sedan appear perilously close to hitting each other. How will the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["No accident will happen", "Head-on collision", "Side-collision", "Rear-end collision"], "answer": 2, "class": "F", "id": 301}
{"question": "The POV car is going down the middle of a three land road. As it comes to an intersection a gray oncoming sedan turns left followed by a blue sedan wherewith the car still going through the intersection. The POV car and the blue sedan appear perilously close to hitting each other. Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["Bicycle or tricycle or non-motor vehicles", "My vehicle", "Bus", "Motorcycle or scooter"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 302}
{"question": "The POV car is going down the middle of a three land road. As it comes to an intersection a gray oncoming sedan turns left followed by a blue sedan wherewith the car still going through the intersection. The POV car and the blue sedan appear perilously close to hitting each other. How much damage will the vehicle(s) receive after collision?", "candidates": ["Nearly no damage", "Some scratches", "Significant deformation"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 303}
{"question": "The POV car is going down the middle of a three land road. As it comes to an intersection a gray oncoming sedan turns left followed by a blue sedan wherewith the car still going through the intersection. The POV car and the blue sedan appear perilously close to hitting each other. Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["Trailer truck or heavy truck", "Mini van or van", "Pickup truck or light truck", "Sedan or general car"], "answer": 3, "class": "F", "id": 304}
{"question": "The POV car is driving down a snowy road. The car enters an intersection. A gray SUV makes a U-turn from the opposite lane into the intersection. The POV car is struggling braking. The POV car is having trouble braking and head straight towards gray suv. Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["Suv or cuv", "Pickup truck or light truck", "Sports car or convertible", "Bus"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 305}
{"question": "The POV car is driving down a snowy road. The car enters an intersection. A gray SUV makes a U-turn from the opposite lane into the intersection. The POV car is struggling braking. The POV car is having trouble braking and head straight towards gray suv. How will the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["Rear-end collision", "Others", "No accident will happen", "Head-on collision"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 306}
{"question": "The POV car is driving down a snowy road. The car enters an intersection. A gray SUV makes a U-turn from the opposite lane into the intersection. The POV car is struggling braking. The POV car is having trouble braking and head straight towards gray suv. Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["Mini van or van", "Motorcycle or scooter", "My vehicle", "Bicycle or tricycle or non-motor vehicles"], "answer": 2, "class": "F", "id": 307}
{"question": "The POV car is driving down a snowy road. The car enters an intersection. A gray SUV makes a U-turn from the opposite lane into the intersection. The POV car is struggling braking. The POV car is having trouble braking and head straight towards gray suv. Are there any vehicles at a risk of an accident?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 308}
{"question": "The POV car is driving in the rightmost lane. The POV car is driving and approaching the intersection. The gray van starts to enter the right lane, cutting off the POV car. The POV car is driving too fast to stop as the gray van approaches. How will the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["Rear-end collision", "Head-on collision", "The vehicle collided with road infrastructure.", "Side-collision"], "answer": 3, "class": "F", "id": 309}
{"question": "The POV car is driving in the rightmost lane. The POV car is driving and approaching the intersection. The gray van starts to enter the right lane, cutting off the POV car. The POV car is driving too fast to stop as the gray van approaches. How much damage will the vehicle(s) receive after collision?", "candidates": ["Nearly no damage", "Some scratches", "Significant deformation"], "answer": 2, "class": "F", "id": 310}
{"question": "The POV car is driving in the rightmost lane. The POV car is driving and approaching the intersection. The gray van starts to enter the right lane, cutting off the POV car. The POV car is driving too fast to stop as the gray van approaches. Are there any vehicles about to change lane or turn?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 311}
{"question": "The POV car is driving in the rightmost lane. The POV car is driving and approaching the intersection. The gray van starts to enter the right lane, cutting off the POV car. The POV car is driving too fast to stop as the gray van approaches. How many vehicles will be involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["None", "Three to five", "Two", "One"], "answer": 2, "class": "F", "id": 312}
{"question": "The POV car is driving in the rightmost lane. The POV car is driving and approaching the intersection. The gray van starts to enter the right lane, cutting off the POV car. The POV car is driving too fast to stop as the gray van approaches. Will the vehicles in front able to stop in time before colliding with other vehicles?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 313}
{"question": "A multiple-lane motorway with multiple cars visible. A pickup in a right lane is quickly approaching a slowed-down sedan in front. The pickup gets dangerously close to the sedan as it is braking as hard as possible. Will there be any vehicle(s) rollover crashing?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 314}
{"question": "A multiple-lane motorway with multiple cars visible. A pickup in a right lane is quickly approaching a slowed-down sedan in front. The pickup gets dangerously close to the sedan as it is braking as hard as possible. Judging by the speed of my vehicle, will my vehicle crash into other vehicles?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 315}
{"question": "A multiple-lane motorway with multiple cars visible. A pickup in a right lane is quickly approaching a slowed-down sedan in front. The pickup gets dangerously close to the sedan as it is braking as hard as possible. Which vehicles are about to cause an accident?", "candidates": ["Sports car or convertible", "Sedan or general car"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 316}
{"question": "A multiple-lane motorway with multiple cars visible. A pickup in a right lane is quickly approaching a slowed-down sedan in front. The pickup gets dangerously close to the sedan as it is braking as hard as possible. Which vehicles are about to cause an accident?", "candidates": ["Mini van or van", "My vehicle", "Bus", "Pickup truck or light truck"], "answer": 3, "class": "F", "id": 317}
{"question": "A multiple-lane motorway with multiple cars visible. A pickup in a right lane is quickly approaching a slowed-down sedan in front. The pickup gets dangerously close to the sedan as it is braking as hard as possible. How much damage will the vehicle(s) receive after collision?", "candidates": ["Some scratches", "Significant deformation", "Nearly no damage"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 318}
{"question": "The POV car is driving through a parking garage. A silver sedan begins to move from a parking space. The silver sedan enters the path of the car. The POV car doesn't decelerate. How many vehicles will be involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["One", "Two", "Three to five", "None"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 319}
{"question": "The POV car is driving through a parking garage. A silver sedan begins to move from a parking space. The silver sedan enters the path of the car. The POV car doesn't decelerate. How will the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["Ran-off-road collision", "Side-collision", "Others", "The vehicle collided with road infrastructure."], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 320}
{"question": "The POV car is driving through a parking garage. A silver sedan begins to move from a parking space. The silver sedan enters the path of the car. The POV car doesn't decelerate. Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["Trailer Truck / Heavy Truck", "My vehicle", "Pickup Truck / Light Truck", "Bus"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 321}
{"question": "The POV car is driving through a parking garage. A silver sedan begins to move from a parking space. The silver sedan enters the path of the car. The POV car doesn't decelerate. Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["Sedan / General Car", "Motorcycle / Scooter", "SUV / CUV", "Mini Van / Van"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 322}
{"question": "The car is travelling on a snowy road. A white sedan and truck can be seen from a distance. The truck has lost its balance. The white sedan behind applied the brake, and the red signals are on. Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["Sports car or convertible", "Trailer truck or heavy truck", "Suv or cuv", "My vehicle"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 323}
{"question": "The car is travelling on a snowy road. A white sedan and truck can be seen from a distance. The truck has lost its balance. The white sedan behind applied the brake, and the red signals are on. How will the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["No collision will happen", "Ran-off-road collision", "Rear-end collision", "Side-collision"], "answer": 3, "class": "F", "id": 324}
{"question": "The car is travelling on a snowy road. A white sedan and truck can be seen from a distance. The truck has lost its balance. The white sedan behind applied the brake, and the red signals are on. Could the accident be prevented if the weather is suitable for driving?", "candidates": ["No, that was not the main cause of the accident", "Yes"], "answer": 1, "class": "I", "id": 325}
{"question": "The POV vehicle is travelling in the middle lane. A red sedan passes the vehicle in the left lane travelling at a much higher speed. The red sedan then immediately hits the brake, slowing and forcing a grey sedan directly behind to swerve to the left and lose control. The grey sedan merges into the leftmost lane and does not appear to have control of the vehicle. Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["Trailer truck or heavy truck", "Sedan or general car", "Suv or cuv", "Bicycle or tricycle or non-motor vehicles"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 326}
{"question": "The POV vehicle is travelling in the middle lane. A red sedan passes the vehicle in the left lane travelling at a much higher speed. The red sedan then immediately hits the brake, slowing and forcing a grey sedan directly behind to swerve to the left and lose control. The grey sedan merges into the leftmost lane and does not appear to have control of the vehicle. Judging by the speed of the fastest vehicle, will it cause an accident?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 327}
{"question": "The POV vehicle is travelling in the middle lane. A red sedan passes the vehicle in the left lane travelling at a much higher speed. The red sedan then immediately hits the brake, slowing and forcing a grey sedan directly behind to swerve to the left and lose control. The grey sedan merges into the leftmost lane and does not appear to have control of the vehicle. Will all vehicles able to safely avoid an accident?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 328}
{"question": "A motorcycle is driving rapidly along a narrow two lane road surrounded by mountains. The motorcycle continues driving quickly forwards. A wild animal suddenly runs into the road from the left side of the motorcycle. The wild animal gets very close to the motorcycle as the motorcycle continues moving rapidly forwards. Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["Trailer truck or heavy truck", "Bus", "Mini van or van", "Motorcycle or scooter"], "answer": 3, "class": "F", "id": 329}
{"question": "A motorcycle is driving rapidly along a narrow two lane road surrounded by mountains. The motorcycle continues driving quickly forwards. A wild animal suddenly runs into the road from the left side of the motorcycle. The wild animal gets very close to the motorcycle as the motorcycle continues moving rapidly forwards. Will there be any vehicle(s) crashing?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 330}
{"question": "A motorcycle is driving rapidly along a narrow two lane road surrounded by mountains. The motorcycle continues driving quickly forwards. A wild animal suddenly runs into the road from the left side of the motorcycle. The wild animal gets very close to the motorcycle as the motorcycle continues moving rapidly forwards. How many vehicles will be involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Two", "Three to five", "One", "None"], "answer": 2, "class": "F", "id": 331}
{"question": "A darkly colored sedan in the left turn lane waits for a traffic light to turn green. The darkly colored sedan in the left turn lane proceeds to enter the intersection on a red light. Several other vehicles enter the intersection from both parallel directions. The darkly colored sedan is going to crash with the cars coming from parallel directions. How will the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["Ran-off-road collision", "The vehicle collided with road infrastructure.", "Side-collision", "Head-on collision"], "answer": 2, "class": "F", "id": 332}
{"question": "A darkly colored sedan in the left turn lane waits for a traffic light to turn green. The darkly colored sedan in the left turn lane proceeds to enter the intersection on a red light. Several other vehicles enter the intersection from both parallel directions. The darkly colored sedan is going to crash with the cars coming from parallel directions. Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["Motorcycle or scooter", "Sedan or general car", "Pickup truck or light truck", "Sports car or convertible"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 333}
{"question": "A white sedan is about to enter an intersection as a white van a bit further ahead is about to clear the intersection. The white sedan passes through the intersection as the white van is on the other side of the intersection. The white sedan and white van both continue driving forwards at a fair rate of speed. Are there any vehicles going to make a stop?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes, the braking light can be seen"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 334}
{"question": "A white sedan is about to enter an intersection as a white van a bit further ahead is about to clear the intersection. The white sedan passes through the intersection as the white van is on the other side of the intersection. The white sedan and white van both continue driving forwards at a fair rate of speed. Are there any vehicles at a risk of an accident?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 335}
{"question": "A white sedan is about to enter an intersection as a white van a bit further ahead is about to clear the intersection. The white sedan passes through the intersection as the white van is on the other side of the intersection. The white sedan and white van both continue driving forwards at a fair rate of speed. Which vehicles are about to stop?", "candidates": ["None", "My vehicle", "Bus", "Pickup truck or light truck"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 336}
{"question": "A white sedan is about to enter an intersection as a white van a bit further ahead is about to clear the intersection. The white sedan passes through the intersection as the white van is on the other side of the intersection. The white sedan and white van both continue driving forwards at a fair rate of speed. Are there any vehicles about to turn?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes, the vehicle is signalling a turn"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 337}
{"question": "Snow is falling. Two trucks enter the intersection from the left side side by side. Two trucks lose control and crash on each other. Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["Bicycle or tricycle or non-motor vehicles", "Suv or cuv", "Trailer truck or heavy truck", "My vehicle"], "answer": 2, "class": "F", "id": 338}
{"question": "Snow is falling. Two trucks enter the intersection from the left side side by side. Two trucks lose control and crash on each other. How many vehicles will be involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["None", "One", "Three to five", "Two"], "answer": 3, "class": "F", "id": 339}
{"question": "Snow is falling. Two trucks enter the intersection from the left side side by side. Two trucks lose control and crash on each other. Will the vehicles in front able to stop in time before colliding with other vehicles?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 340}
{"question": "The POV car is travelling in the left lane. The POV car attempts to turn left onto another road. The POV car waits for a white sedan in the opposite lane to pass before turning. The POV car begins to make a left hand turn across traffic. Judging by the speed of my vehicle, will my vehicle crash into other vehicles?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 341}
{"question": "The POV car is travelling in the left lane. The POV car attempts to turn left onto another road. The POV car waits for a white sedan in the opposite lane to pass before turning. The POV car begins to make a left hand turn across traffic. Which vehicles are about to stop?", "candidates": ["Mini van or van", "None", "My vehicle", "Sedan or general car"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 342}
{"question": "The POV car is travelling in the left lane. The POV car attempts to turn left onto another road. The POV car waits for a white sedan in the opposite lane to pass before turning. The POV car begins to make a left hand turn across traffic. Judging by the speed of the fastest vehicle, will it cause an accident?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 343}
{"question": "The POV car is travelling in the left lane. The POV car attempts to turn left onto another road. The POV car waits for a white sedan in the opposite lane to pass before turning. The POV car begins to make a left hand turn across traffic. Are there any vehicles at a risk of an accident?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 344}
{"question": "The POV car is driving down a rainy road at night. The windshield wipers engage. The windshield is smeared with water and makes visibility difficult. A yellow scooter approaches the vehicle right from the front. It is too late for the POV car to stop in time. Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["Pickup truck or light truck", "Bicycle or tricycle or scooter", "Bus", "Sedan or general car"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 345}
{"question": "The POV car is driving down a rainy road at night. The windshield wipers engage. The windshield is smeared with water and makes visibility difficult. A yellow scooter approaches the vehicle right from the front. It is too late for the POV car to stop in time. Are there any vehicles at a risk of an accident?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 346}
{"question": "The POV car is driving down a rainy road at night. The windshield wipers engage. The windshield is smeared with water and makes visibility difficult. A yellow scooter approaches the vehicle right from the front. It is too late for the POV car to stop in time. Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["Trailer truck or heavy truck", "My vehicle", "Sports car or convertible", "Bus"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 347}
{"question": "A black Mini Cooper is entering an intersection. The left turn signal is blinking on the black Mini Cooper. The black Mini Cooper passes the intersection and begins turning left. The black Mini Cooper quickly comes to a rest when a red motorcycle enters the second intersection that the black Mini Cooper is crossing in front of the black Mini Cooper. The red motorcycle passes through the intersection as the black Mini Cooper remains still. Will there be any vehicle(s) rollover crashing?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 348}
{"question": "A black Mini Cooper is entering an intersection. The left turn signal is blinking on the black Mini Cooper. The black Mini Cooper passes the intersection and begins turning left. The black Mini Cooper quickly comes to a rest when a red motorcycle enters the second intersection that the black Mini Cooper is crossing in front of the black Mini Cooper. The red motorcycle passes through the intersection as the black Mini Cooper remains still. Are there any vehicles about to change lane or turn?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 349}
{"question": "The POV car is in the right hand lane with a thin sheet of snow on the grund. There is a trail of three vehicles ahead in the other lane. The POV car is going far faster than the vehicles in the other lane despite driving in a worse conditioned lane. A white Nissan Cube switches to the POV car's lane and the POV car is not able to slow on time because it is going too fast. Will my vehicle be able to stop in time before colliding with other vehicles?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 350}
{"question": "The POV car is in the right hand lane with a thin sheet of snow on the grund. There is a trail of three vehicles ahead in the other lane. The POV car is going far faster than the vehicles in the other lane despite driving in a worse conditioned lane. A white Nissan Cube switches to the POV car's lane and the POV car is not able to slow on time because it is going too fast. How much damage will the vehicle(s) receive after collision?", "candidates": ["Significant deformation", "Some scratches", "Nearly no damage"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 351}
{"question": "The POV car is in the right hand lane with a thin sheet of snow on the grund. There is a trail of three vehicles ahead in the other lane. The POV car is going far faster than the vehicles in the other lane despite driving in a worse conditioned lane. A white Nissan Cube switches to the POV car's lane and the POV car is not able to slow on time because it is going too fast. How will the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["The vehicle collided with road infrastructure.", "Ran-off-road collision", "Rear-end collision", "Side-collision"], "answer": 2, "class": "F", "id": 352}
{"question": "The POV car is in the right hand lane with a thin sheet of snow on the grund. There is a trail of three vehicles ahead in the other lane. The POV car is going far faster than the vehicles in the other lane despite driving in a worse conditioned lane. A white Nissan Cube switches to the POV car's lane and the POV car is not able to slow on time because it is going too fast. How many vehicles will be involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Three to five", "None", "One", "Two"], "answer": 3, "class": "F", "id": 353}
{"question": "The POV car is in the right hand lane with a thin sheet of snow on the grund. There is a trail of three vehicles ahead in the other lane. The POV car is going far faster than the vehicles in the other lane despite driving in a worse conditioned lane. A white Nissan Cube switches to the POV car's lane and the POV car is not able to slow on time because it is going too fast. Judging by the speed of my vehicle, will my vehicle crash into other vehicles?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 354}
{"question": "The POV car is driving as a silver car passes it. The motorbike with three people passed after the sliver car on the left has a man in a white shirt who looks like he is not able to stay on the bike.  Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["Motorcycle or scooter", "Bicycle or tricycle or non-motor vehicles", "Bus", "Pickup truck or light truck"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 355}
{"question": "The POV car is driving as a silver car passes it. The motorbike with three people passed after the sliver car on the left has a man in a white shirt who looks like he is not able to stay on the bike.  Will all vehicles able to safely avoid an accident?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 356}
{"question": "A white compact car slowly starts pullling into a stall at a mechanic's shop. The white compact car pulls into the stall at a slight angle as a man in a black shirt watches and signals the driver how to proceed. A man in a purple shirt walks up behind the white compact car. The white compact car speeds up quickly going in the direction of the man in a black shirt. Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["Mini van or van", "Bicycle or tricycle or non-motor vehicles", "Sedan or general car", "Bus"], "answer": 2, "class": "F", "id": 357}
{"question": "A white compact car slowly starts pullling into a stall at a mechanic's shop. The white compact car pulls into the stall at a slight angle as a man in a black shirt watches and signals the driver how to proceed. A man in a purple shirt walks up behind the white compact car. The white compact car speeds up quickly going in the direction of the man in a black shirt. Will there be any vehicle(s) rollover crashing?", "candidates": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 358}
{"question": "A white compact car slowly starts pullling into a stall at a mechanic's shop. The white compact car pulls into the stall at a slight angle as a man in a black shirt watches and signals the driver how to proceed. A man in a purple shirt walks up behind the white compact car. The white compact car speeds up quickly going in the direction of the man in a black shirt. Will all vehicles able to safely avoid an accident?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 359}
{"question": "A white compact car slowly starts pullling into a stall at a mechanic's shop. The white compact car pulls into the stall at a slight angle as a man in a black shirt watches and signals the driver how to proceed. A man in a purple shirt walks up behind the white compact car. The white compact car speeds up quickly going in the direction of the man in a black shirt. What accident is about to happen?", "candidates": ["Collosion with building", "Side collision", "collosion with pedestrain"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 360}
{"question": "The POV car is driving behind a white bus. The white bus has on flashing lights. a black SUV passes in the right lane. The lights on the bus in front of The POV car flash more. Will there be any vehicle(s) rollover crashing?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 361}
{"question": "The POV car is driving behind a white bus. The white bus has on flashing lights. a black SUV passes in the right lane. The lights on the bus in front of The POV car flash more. Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["Bicycle or tricycle or non-motor vehicles", "Bus", "Mini van or van", "Sports car or convertible"], "answer": 2, "class": "F", "id": 362}
{"question": "The POV car is driving behind a white bus. The white bus has on flashing lights. a black SUV passes in the right lane. The lights on the bus in front of The POV car flash more. How many vehicles will be involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["One", "Three to five", "Two", "None"], "answer": 1, "class": "F", "id": 363}
{"question": "The POV car is driving behind a white bus. The white bus has on flashing lights. a black SUV passes in the right lane. The lights on the bus in front of The POV car flash more. Which vehicles are about to be involved in an accident?", "candidates": ["Trailer truck or heavy truck", "Motorcycle or scooter"], "answer": 0, "class": "F", "id": 364}
{"question": "A lightly colored sedan is driving slowly in the right lane. A motorcycle is driving quickly behind the lightly colored sedan. The motorcycle continues going quickly and hits the lightly colored sedan. Items from the motorcycle are thrown and the motorcycle falls over. The lightly colored sedan remains paused while the motorcyclist gets up. Which could be the reason for this accident?", "candidates": ["Traffic congestion", "Road safety negligence", "Others", "Obstructed view or limited visibility"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 365}
{"question": "A lightly colored sedan is driving slowly in the right lane. A motorcycle is driving quickly behind the lightly colored sedan. The motorcycle continues going quickly and hits the lightly colored sedan. Items from the motorcycle are thrown and the motorcycle falls over. The lightly colored sedan remains paused while the motorcyclist gets up. Would the accident still happen if there are less vehicles on the road?", "candidates": ["No, there would be more space to safely avoid the accident", "Yes, the involved vehicles would still violate traffic rules"], "answer": 0, "class": "C", "id": 366}
{"question": "A lightly colored sedan is driving slowly in the right lane. A motorcycle is driving quickly behind the lightly colored sedan. The motorcycle continues going quickly and hits the lightly colored sedan. Items from the motorcycle are thrown and the motorcycle falls over. The lightly colored sedan remains paused while the motorcyclist gets up. How did the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["No accident happened", "Head-on collision", "Rear-end collision", "Ran-off-road collision"], "answer": 2, "class": "R", "id": 367}
{"question": "The POV car driving to the side while a passing pickup is acceleraring down the road. The car moves to the left side of the road and stop. The POV car is crashed by the truck. The pickup keeps speeding downn the curved road. How fast did the vehicles involved in the accident move before they crash, based on the speed of the fastest one?", "candidates": ["Roughly the same as other vehicles", "Faster than other vehicles", "Slower than other vehicles"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 368}
{"question": "The POV car driving to the side while a passing pickup is acceleraring down the road. The car moves to the left side of the road and stop. The POV car is crashed by the truck. The pickup keeps speeding downn the curved road. What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Pickup truck or light truck", "Sedan or general car", "Bus", "Others"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 369}
{"question": "The POV car driving to the side while a passing pickup is acceleraring down the road. The car moves to the left side of the road and stop. The POV car is crashed by the truck. The pickup keeps speeding downn the curved road. How many vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["More than five", "One", "Two", "Three to five"], "answer": 2, "class": "R", "id": 370}
{"question": "The POV car driving to the side while a passing pickup is acceleraring down the road. The car moves to the left side of the road and stop. The POV car is crashed by the truck. The pickup keeps speeding downn the curved road. What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["My vehicle", "Motorcycle or scooter", "Sports car or convertible", "Trailer truck or heavy truck"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 371}
{"question": "The POV car driving to the side while a passing pickup is acceleraring down the road. The car moves to the left side of the road and stop. The POV car is crashed by the truck. The pickup keeps speeding downn the curved road. Did the accident happen when the involved vehicles were speeding?", "candidates": ["Yes, the invovled vehicles were badly damaged", "Yes, the involved vehicles continued to speed away", "No"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 372}
{"question": "The left turn signal is blinking on a white SUV that is paused at an intersection on a steep hill. The POV car is behind the white SUV. The white SUV starts slowly rolling backwards. The POV car moves backwards in reaction. The white SUV starts moving backwards fairly quickly causing the white sedan to move backwards giving an excess amount of space. The brakes are applied on the white SUV causing the white SUV to remain still. How did the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["Head-on collision", "Side-collision", "Ran-off-road collision", "No accident happened"], "answer": 3, "class": "R", "id": 373}
{"question": "The left turn signal is blinking on a white SUV that is paused at an intersection on a steep hill. The POV car is behind the white SUV. The white SUV starts slowly rolling backwards. The POV car moves backwards in reaction. The white SUV starts moving backwards fairly quickly causing the white sedan to move backwards giving an excess amount of space. The brakes are applied on the white SUV causing the white SUV to remain still. Did any vehicle(s) try to steer away or stop before crashing?", "candidates": ["Yes, the involved vehicles received nearly no damge", "No, the invovled vehicles were badly damaged"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 374}
{"question": "The POV car has hit the silver SUV which is badly damaged. The POV car spins to the left and stops in front of the black car. The POV car stops while pointed at the black car. Did an accident happen?", "candidates": ["Yes, the vehicle(s) are in unusual positions", "Yes, there are visible damages", "No, no vehicles receive any damage"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 375}
{"question": "The POV car has hit the silver SUV which is badly damaged. The POV car spins to the left and stops in front of the black car. The POV car stops while pointed at the black car. Did the accident happen when the involved vehicles were speeding?", "candidates": ["Yes, the involved vehicles continued to speed away", "Yes, the invovled vehicles were badly damaged", "No"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 376}
{"question": "The POV car has hit the silver SUV which is badly damaged. The POV car spins to the left and stops in front of the black car. The POV car stops while pointed at the black car. What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Sports car or convertible", "Bus", "Trailer truck or heavy truck", "My vehicle"], "answer": 3, "class": "R", "id": 377}
{"question": "The POV car has hit the silver SUV which is badly damaged. The POV car spins to the left and stops in front of the black car. The POV car stops while pointed at the black car. What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Suv or cuv", "Mini van or van", "Motorcycle or scooter", "Sedan or general car"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 378}
{"question": "The truck merge its lane to the left. The truck got extremely close to a black sedan. The truck hits the black sedan from its back. The black sedan slides uncontrollably, spinning 90 degrees to the left. Thr black sedan gets sideways into the truck's path. Which could be the reason for this accident?", "candidates": ["Traffic congestion", "Improper lane change", "Speeding vehicles", "No accident happened"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 379}
{"question": "The truck merge its lane to the left. The truck got extremely close to a black sedan. The truck hits the black sedan from its back. The black sedan slides uncontrollably, spinning 90 degrees to the left. Thr black sedan gets sideways into the truck's path. How did the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["Side-collision", "Head-on collision", "The vehicle collided with road infrastructure.", "Ran-off-road collision"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 380}
{"question": "The truck merge its lane to the left. The truck got extremely close to a black sedan. The truck hits the black sedan from its back. The black sedan slides uncontrollably, spinning 90 degrees to the left. Thr black sedan gets sideways into the truck's path. Did an accident happen?", "candidates": ["No, no vehicles receive any damage", "Yes, the vehicle(s) are in unusual positions", "Yes, there are visible damages"], "answer": 2, "class": "R", "id": 381}
{"question": "A white suv hits a black sedan infront of it in a traffic jam. Visiable damage can be seem on the back of the black sedan. The POV car is in the back if the white SUV. The POV car just stopped. What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Mini van or van", "My vehicle", "Motorcycle or scooter", "Trailer truck or heavy truck"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 382}
{"question": "A white suv hits a black sedan infront of it in a traffic jam. Visiable damage can be seem on the back of the black sedan. The POV car is in the back if the white SUV. The POV car just stopped. How did the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["Side-collision", "Rear-end collision", "Ran-off-road collision", "The vehicle collided with road infrastructure."], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 383}
{"question": "A white suv hits a black sedan infront of it in a traffic jam. Visiable damage can be seem on the back of the black sedan. The POV car is in the back if the white SUV. The POV car just stopped. Which could be the reason for this accident?", "candidates": ["Traffic light violation", "Others", "Road safety negligence", "Improper lane change"], "answer": 2, "class": "R", "id": 384}
{"question": "A white suv hits a black sedan infront of it in a traffic jam. Visiable damage can be seem on the back of the black sedan. The POV car is in the back if the white SUV. The POV car just stopped. What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Others", "Pickup truck or light truck", "Suv or cuv", "Bus"], "answer": 2, "class": "R", "id": 385}
{"question": "A red sedan drives straight and then turns left. A truck coming from opposite direction directly collides with red car.  What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Pickup truck or light truck", "My vehicle", "Motorcycle or scooter", "Bus"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 386}
{"question": "A red sedan drives straight and then turns left. A truck coming from opposite direction directly collides with red car.  Which could be the reason for this accident?", "candidates": ["Obstructed view or limited visibility", "Traffic light violation", "Road safety negligence", "Traffic rules violation"], "answer": 2, "class": "R", "id": 387}
{"question": "A red sedan drives straight and then turns left. A truck coming from opposite direction directly collides with red car.  How many vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Three to five", "Two", "None", "One"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 388}
{"question": "A dark green van is moving in front of the POV car. The POV car has a abnormal clos distance with the dark green van.  The dark green van suddenly stops. What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Bus", "Pickup truck or light truck", "My vehicle", "Trailer truck or heavy truck"], "answer": 2, "class": "R", "id": 389}
{"question": "A dark green van is moving in front of the POV car. The POV car has a abnormal clos distance with the dark green van.  The dark green van suddenly stops. Did the accident happen when the involved vehicles were speeding?", "candidates": ["No", "Yes, the involved vehicles continued to speed away", "Yes, the invovled vehicles were badly damaged"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 390}
{"question": "A dark green van is moving in front of the POV car. The POV car has a abnormal clos distance with the dark green van.  The dark green van suddenly stops. How many vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Two", "One", "More than five", "None"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 391}
{"question": "A dark green van is moving in front of the POV car. The POV car has a abnormal clos distance with the dark green van.  The dark green van suddenly stops. What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Motorcycle or scooter", "Sedan or general car", "Mini van or van", "Others"], "answer": 2, "class": "R", "id": 392}
{"question": "The POV car is approaching an intersection. A motorcycle is standing immediatly in front of the POV car preparing to go in front of the vehicle. The vehicle continues moving and strikes the motrocycle. The woman trys to swerve right to avoid the POV but fails. Both the motorcycle and the woman riding the motorcycle fall down. The vehicle comes to a rest as the woman begins to stand up. What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Sports car or convertible", "Trailer truck or heavy truck", "Others", "Motorcycle or scooter"], "answer": 3, "class": "R", "id": 393}
{"question": "The POV car is approaching an intersection. A motorcycle is standing immediatly in front of the POV car preparing to go in front of the vehicle. The vehicle continues moving and strikes the motrocycle. The woman trys to swerve right to avoid the POV but fails. Both the motorcycle and the woman riding the motorcycle fall down. The vehicle comes to a rest as the woman begins to stand up. Which could be the reason for this accident?", "candidates": ["Speeding vehicles", "Improper lane change", "Traffic rules violation", "No accident happened"], "answer": 2, "class": "R", "id": 394}
{"question": "The POV car is approaching an intersection. A motorcycle is standing immediatly in front of the POV car preparing to go in front of the vehicle. The vehicle continues moving and strikes the motrocycle. The woman trys to swerve right to avoid the POV but fails. Both the motorcycle and the woman riding the motorcycle fall down. The vehicle comes to a rest as the woman begins to stand up. Did any vehicle(s) try to steer away or stop before crashing?", "candidates": ["Yes,", "No, the invovled vehicles were badly damaged"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 395}
{"question": "The POV car is approaching an intersection. A motorcycle is standing immediatly in front of the POV car preparing to go in front of the vehicle. The vehicle continues moving and strikes the motrocycle. The woman trys to swerve right to avoid the POV but fails. Both the motorcycle and the woman riding the motorcycle fall down. The vehicle comes to a rest as the woman begins to stand up. What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Pickup truck or light truck", "Bus", "Mini van or van", "My vehicle"], "answer": 3, "class": "R", "id": 396}
{"question": "The POV car appears to be very close to a dark sedan. The dark sedan quickly gains some distance ahead of the car. The POV car then matches the sedan's speed. The POV car maintains a steady distance from the sedan. Which could be the reason for this accident?", "candidates": ["Traffic light violation", "No accident happened", "Traffic congestion", "Obstructed view or limited visibility"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 397}
{"question": "The POV car appears to be very close to a dark sedan. The dark sedan quickly gains some distance ahead of the car. The POV car then matches the sedan's speed. The POV car maintains a steady distance from the sedan. How many vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Three to five", "None", "Two", "One"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 398}
{"question": "The POV car appears to be very close to a dark sedan. The dark sedan quickly gains some distance ahead of the car. The POV car then matches the sedan's speed. The POV car maintains a steady distance from the sedan. Which could be the reason for this accident?", "candidates": ["Road safety negligence", "Others", "Speeding vehicles", "No accident happened"], "answer": 3, "class": "R", "id": 399}
{"question": "The POV car appears to be very close to a dark sedan. The dark sedan quickly gains some distance ahead of the car. The POV car then matches the sedan's speed. The POV car maintains a steady distance from the sedan. How did the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["Others", "No accident happened", "Side-collision", "Ran-off-road collision"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 400}
{"question": "The POV car appears to be very close to a dark sedan. The dark sedan quickly gains some distance ahead of the car. The POV car then matches the sedan's speed. The POV car maintains a steady distance from the sedan. Which could be the reason for this accident?", "candidates": ["No accident happened", "Traffic rules violation", "Retrograde vehicles", "Improper lane change"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 401}
{"question": "The POV car appears to be very close to a dark sedan. The dark sedan quickly gains some distance ahead of the car. The POV car then matches the sedan's speed. The POV car maintains a steady distance from the sedan. How did the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["No accident happened", "Head-on collision", "The vehicle collided with road infrastructure.", "Rear-end collision"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 402}
{"question": "A black sedan and white SUV crash under a bridge. The SUV's head is badly damaged. The black sedan is pushed forward to the left and passes in front of an intersection where several vehicles are waiting for a red light. The white SUV is pushed to the left and quickly pauses on a grassy median. How did the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["Others", "The vehicle collided with road infrastructure.", "Ran-off-road collision", "Side-collision"], "answer": 3, "class": "R", "id": 403}
{"question": "A black sedan and white SUV crash under a bridge. The SUV's head is badly damaged. The black sedan is pushed forward to the left and passes in front of an intersection where several vehicles are waiting for a red light. The white SUV is pushed to the left and quickly pauses on a grassy median. Did an accident happen?", "candidates": ["No, no vehicles receive any damage", "Yes, there are visible damages"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 404}
{"question": "A black sedan and white SUV crash under a bridge. The SUV's head is badly damaged. The black sedan is pushed forward to the left and passes in front of an intersection where several vehicles are waiting for a red light. The white SUV is pushed to the left and quickly pauses on a grassy median. Which could be the reason for this accident?", "candidates": ["Speeding vehicles", "Improper lane change"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 405}
{"question": "A silver van is holding still in the middle of the road. The right turn signal of the silver van is blinking. A black SUV comes skidding very quickly down the road and crashes into the silver van. The silver van is pushed forwards into the grass on the side of the road. The black SUV continues straight spinning very quickly losing a tire and some glass in the process. The silver van comes to a rest on the side of the road. The blcak SUV comes to a rest in the middle of the road facing the opposite direction. Which could be the reason for this accident?", "candidates": ["Road safety negligence", "No accident happened", "Traffic light violation", "Slippy road surface"], "answer": 3, "class": "R", "id": 406}
{"question": "A silver van is holding still in the middle of the road. The right turn signal of the silver van is blinking. A black SUV comes skidding very quickly down the road and crashes into the silver van. The silver van is pushed forwards into the grass on the side of the road. The black SUV continues straight spinning very quickly losing a tire and some glass in the process. The silver van comes to a rest on the side of the road. The blcak SUV comes to a rest in the middle of the road facing the opposite direction. What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["SUV / CUV", "Pickup Truck / Light Truck", "Others", "My vehicle"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 407}
{"question": "A silver van is holding still in the middle of the road. The right turn signal of the silver van is blinking. A black SUV comes skidding very quickly down the road and crashes into the silver van. The silver van is pushed forwards into the grass on the side of the road. The black SUV continues straight spinning very quickly losing a tire and some glass in the process. The silver van comes to a rest on the side of the road. The blcak SUV comes to a rest in the middle of the road facing the opposite direction. Did an accident happen?", "candidates": ["Yes, there are visible damages", "No, no vehicles receive any damage", "Yes, the vehicle(s) are in unusual positions"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 408}
{"question": "The white car crashed on the side of the road and police car next to it. The police officer get's out of the police car. Which could be the reason for this accident?", "candidates": ["Speeding vehicles", "Traffic rules violation", "Retrograde vehicles", "Traffic light violation"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 409}
{"question": "The white car crashed on the side of the road and police car next to it. The police officer get's out of the police car. What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Sedan or general car", "Motorcycle or scooter", "Sports car or convertible", "My vehicle"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 410}
{"question": "The is a white SUV ahead with a white sedan to the right on the white SUV. The white sedan begins back up and hits the white SUV. The white sedan pauses immediately while the white SUV continues traveling slightly before pausing. The black sedan pauses as both the white SUV and white sedan pause ahead. Which could be the reason for this accident?", "candidates": ["No accident happened", "Obstructed view or limited visibility", "Retrograde vehicles", "Speeding vehicles"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 411}
{"question": "The is a white SUV ahead with a white sedan to the right on the white SUV. The white sedan begins back up and hits the white SUV. The white sedan pauses immediately while the white SUV continues traveling slightly before pausing. The black sedan pauses as both the white SUV and white sedan pause ahead. Did the accident happen when the involved vehicles were speeding?", "candidates": ["Yes, the invovled vehicles were badly damaged", "Yes, the involved vehicles continued to speed away", "No"], "answer": 2, "class": "R", "id": 412}
{"question": "The is a white SUV ahead with a white sedan to the right on the white SUV. The white sedan begins back up and hits the white SUV. The white sedan pauses immediately while the white SUV continues traveling slightly before pausing. The black sedan pauses as both the white SUV and white sedan pause ahead. What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Pickup Truck / Light Truck", "Trailer Truck / Heavy Truck", "Mini Van / Van", "SUV / CUV"], "answer": 3, "class": "R", "id": 413}
{"question": "The is a white SUV ahead with a white sedan to the right on the white SUV. The white sedan begins back up and hits the white SUV. The white sedan pauses immediately while the white SUV continues traveling slightly before pausing. The black sedan pauses as both the white SUV and white sedan pause ahead. What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Motorcycle / Scooter", "My vehicle", "Sedan / General Car", "Bus"], "answer": 2, "class": "R", "id": 414}
{"question": "The POV car is driving forwards slowly in the left lane of a bridge. A green truck is driving forwards in the right lane of a bridge next to the black sedan. The green truck moves into the left lane hitting the black sedan. The green truck continues moving further to the left hitting the wall of the bridge. The green truck bounces back into the left lane before moving back on to the shoulder and slowly slowing down. The black sedan also moves on to the shoulder and slows down. The green truck comes to a rest on the shoulder as the black sedan slows down on the shoulder. What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Mini Van / Van", "Others", "SUV / CUV", "Pickup Truck / Light Truck"], "answer": 3, "class": "R", "id": 415}
{"question": "The POV car is driving forwards slowly in the left lane of a bridge. A green truck is driving forwards in the right lane of a bridge next to the black sedan. The green truck moves into the left lane hitting the black sedan. The green truck continues moving further to the left hitting the wall of the bridge. The green truck bounces back into the left lane before moving back on to the shoulder and slowly slowing down. The black sedan also moves on to the shoulder and slows down. The green truck comes to a rest on the shoulder as the black sedan slows down on the shoulder. What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Sedan / General Car", "Trailer Truck / Heavy Truck", "My vehicle", "Bicycle / Tricycle / Non-motor Vehicles"], "answer": 2, "class": "R", "id": 416}
{"question": "The POV car is driving forwards slowly in the left lane of a bridge. A green truck is driving forwards in the right lane of a bridge next to the black sedan. The green truck moves into the left lane hitting the black sedan. The green truck continues moving further to the left hitting the wall of the bridge. The green truck bounces back into the left lane before moving back on to the shoulder and slowly slowing down. The black sedan also moves on to the shoulder and slows down. The green truck comes to a rest on the shoulder as the black sedan slows down on the shoulder. Which could be the reason for this accident?", "candidates": ["No accident happened", "Improper lane change", "Others", "Traffic light violation"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 417}
{"question": "The POV car is driving forwards slowly in the left lane of a bridge. A green truck is driving forwards in the right lane of a bridge next to the black sedan. The green truck moves into the left lane hitting the black sedan. The green truck continues moving further to the left hitting the wall of the bridge. The green truck bounces back into the left lane before moving back on to the shoulder and slowly slowing down. The black sedan also moves on to the shoulder and slows down. The green truck comes to a rest on the shoulder as the black sedan slows down on the shoulder. How many vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Three to five", "Two", "None", "One"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 418}
{"question": "The POV car is swerving wildly back and forth on a two lane road. The POV car makes a large turn to the left and proceeds to drive backwards briefly in the opposite lane. The POV car then swerves a bit further causes it to fall into a ditch on the side of the road. The POV car continues moving fairly quickly in the ditch before slowly reducing the speed. What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["My vehicle", "Others", "Trailer truck or heavy truck", "Mini van or van"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 419}
{"question": "The POV car is swerving wildly back and forth on a two lane road. The POV car makes a large turn to the left and proceeds to drive backwards briefly in the opposite lane. The POV car then swerves a bit further causes it to fall into a ditch on the side of the road. The POV car continues moving fairly quickly in the ditch before slowly reducing the speed. Which could be the reason for this accident?", "candidates": ["car losing control", "Others", "Obstructed view or limited visibility", "No accident happened"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 420}
{"question": "A red sedan and a white pickup truck are moving at the same speed next to each other. There is stopping traffic in front of the truck. The white truck fails to avoid the stopping traffis because of the red sedan. The white pickup truck collided with the stopping traffic. Which could be the reason for this accident?", "candidates": ["Others", "Retrograde vehicles", "Road safety negligence", "Improper lane change"], "answer": 3, "class": "R", "id": 421}
{"question": "A red sedan and a white pickup truck are moving at the same speed next to each other. There is stopping traffic in front of the truck. The white truck fails to avoid the stopping traffis because of the red sedan. The white pickup truck collided with the stopping traffic. Did an accident happen?", "candidates": ["Yes, there are visible damages", "Yes, the vehicle(s) are in unusual positions", "No, no vehicles receive any damage"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 422}
{"question": "On a busy road, a black sedan is moving toward the right, and a red sedan, a silver sedan, and a black sedan are moving down the left. The black sedan hits the silver sedan, and as a result, the silver sedan hits the red sedan. All three vehicles are damaged. What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Sedan or general car", "Others", "Trailer truck or heavy truck", "Mini van or van"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 423}
{"question": "On a busy road, a black sedan is moving toward the right, and a red sedan, a silver sedan, and a black sedan are moving down the left. The black sedan hits the silver sedan, and as a result, the silver sedan hits the red sedan. All three vehicles are damaged. How did the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["No accident happened", "Others", "Head-on collision", "Rear-end collision"], "answer": 3, "class": "R", "id": 424}
{"question": "On a busy road, a black sedan is moving toward the right, and a red sedan, a silver sedan, and a black sedan are moving down the left. The black sedan hits the silver sedan, and as a result, the silver sedan hits the red sedan. All three vehicles are damaged. What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Motorcycle or scooter", "Sedan or general car", "Bus", "My vehicle"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 425}
{"question": "Two two-wheelers have crashed into each other. When they collide with the road, one person is seriously injured. The other three people are slightly injured. The vehicles are almost completely damaged. What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Sedan or general car", "Pickup truck or light truck", "Motorcycle or scooter", "My vehicle"], "answer": 2, "class": "R", "id": 426}
{"question": "Two two-wheelers have crashed into each other. When they collide with the road, one person is seriously injured. The other three people are slightly injured. The vehicles are almost completely damaged. How did the vehicle(s) crash?", "candidates": ["Head-on collision", "The vehicle collided with road infrastructure.", "No accident happened"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 427}
{"question": "A white sedan is driving forwards under a bridge at a fairly high rate of speed. A white van in front of the white sedan proceeds to drive forwards passing through an intersection. The white van exits the intersection as the white sedan enters the intersection. What types of vehicles just stopped?", "candidates": ["Mini van or van", "None", "My vehicle", "Others"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 428}
{"question": "A white sedan is driving forwards under a bridge at a fairly high rate of speed. A white van in front of the white sedan proceeds to drive forwards passing through an intersection. The white van exits the intersection as the white sedan enters the intersection. What types of vehicles just made a turn?", "candidates": ["None", "Trailer truck or heavy truck", "Sedan or general car", "Suv or cuv"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 429}
{"question": "A white sedan is driving forwards under a bridge at a fairly high rate of speed. A white van in front of the white sedan proceeds to drive forwards passing through an intersection. The white van exits the intersection as the white sedan enters the intersection. Did any vehicles change lane?", "candidates": ["Yes, the vehicle(s) just join a new lane", "No"], "answer": 1, "class": "R", "id": 430}
{"question": "The POV car passes a tow truck. The POV car passes the tow truck on an angle to the right. The POV car is perpendicular to traffic. The POV car is pointed towards the median. Did an accident happen?", "candidates": ["Yes, the vehicle(s) are in unusual positions", "No, no vehicles receive any damage", "Yes, there are visible damages"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 431}
{"question": "The POV car passes a tow truck. The POV car passes the tow truck on an angle to the right. The POV car is perpendicular to traffic. The POV car is pointed towards the median. What types of vehicles were involved in the accident?", "candidates": ["Others", "Trailer truck or heavy truck", "My vehicle", "Mini van or van"], "answer": 2, "class": "R", "id": 432}
{"question": "The POV car passes a tow truck. The POV car passes the tow truck on an angle to the right. The POV car is perpendicular to traffic. The POV car is pointed towards the median. Which could be the reason for this accident?", "candidates": ["Road safety negligence", "Others", "Traffic light violation", "Speeding vehicles"], "answer": 0, "class": "R", "id": 433}